[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
[APPLAUSE]
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC STOPS]
What are you doing?
[SOBBING] It's so heartbreaking.
It's so touching.
Didn't you see it?
You're such drama queens!
That part was still funny.
The crying doesn't come
until the end.
You're such drama queens.
You're all so fake!
You probably didn't even watch
Call Me Mother  in theaters.
Did you?
- We're just thinking ahead.
- I watched it.
We already knew,
so we started crying early.
But you held
a block screening for it, right?
Yeah, because it's funny.
Call Me Mother  is number one
on Netflix Philippines.
- True!
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
It's such a huge hit.
The gay lead was amazing.
I heard he even won Best Actor,
- so that's why I'm crying.
- Yeah!
That's why I really idolize
that gay guy.
Esnyr's really number one.
- Huh?
- Vice, it's you!
Me? I'm amazing!
Did you watch it?
- Of course!
- What's the story about?
I was with you
when I watched it.
- See?
- [VERNA] Oh!
You were behind me
while I was watching.
You even sat in front of me?
[LAUGHTER]
- That movie's so good!
- It really is, Meme,
because I have a crush
on someone in it.
- Who's your crush in the movie?
- That... guy...
- Oh, please!
- I know who your crush is.
- Who?
- Is it John Lapuz?
[LAUGHTER]
- Who?
- No...
- Who is it?
- Who's your crush?
- Just between us, okay?
- [TETAY] Just tell us!
- Brent.
- Oh my God!
- Brent Manalo?
- Yeah.
Hey, I know him!
- Really?
- Yeah, he's Vince's friend.
- Of course.
- You were with him on  PBB.
Yeah, I know him really well.
I was with him for two months.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Why do you have a crush on him?
Well, because, you know...
You know how your crushes
are always guys who definitely
wouldn't like you back?
- Exactly!
- Wow!
It's already game over
at first sight.
Exactly. Even Empoy wouldn't
take a picture with you.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Meme, you'll never know.
Exactly, you'll never know.
You'll never achieve.
- Why...
- Mine's Emilio.
Emilio?
- Yeah.
- Really?
- But Emilio isn't here.
Hacinto? No, I mean
the one from  PBB!
- Where is the hero here?
- I said the one from  PBB!
We're talking about
Call Me Mother!
Yeah, but Brent was with him
on  PBB.
Oh my gosh!
Did you get close to Emilio?
- Yeah, he was my batchmate.
- Oh my God!
Batchmates where?
I'm from La Salle,
he's from Ateneo.
Oh, La Salle and Ateneo?
Fancy!
Why are you into Emilio?
He has this something...
Like, if we met in person,
I feel like we'd really click.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
You know Emilio, right?
Do you think Emilio
would like her?
- It's possible.
- She could be his auntie.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Well... I talked to him.
He said he misses
his uncle in Saudi.
Okay, I'm just going to eat
fish crackers!
- Maybe he'll like you.
- You never know! Come on!
Who are you closer to,
Emilio or Brent?
- Brent.
- [VERNA] Oh!
We're both from La Salle.
- Oh!
- That's why.
It runs in the blood.
Do you have a problem
with Ateneo?
- Not really.
- [TETAY CHUCKLES]-
Look at you with your
"that's why."
[LAUGHTER]
Anyway, this is my
number one movie,
- Call Me Mother.
- Congratulations.
- It's such a beautiful story.
Yes. And it's even
more emotional
when the theme song
starts playing.
The  Tala  version
by Bryan Chong?
Oh!
It's nice because
they were fresh out of PBB then.
They starred in a movie.
It was Brent
together with River.
- Yes.
He was Nadine Lustre's
husband there.
And him too.
They've done a lot of projects.
Was it nice being in  PBB?
Very.
What's your most memorable
experience in  PBB?
Maybe the free air conditioning
and food.
We're trying to save money
nowadays, right?
How many months were you
inside the  PBB  house?
I was there
for two months, Meme.
- Oh, really.
- You got evicted right away.
- Wow.
- I'm sorry, okay?
[LAUGHTER]
Her words sting, don't they?
- Right!
- Your words sting.
I want to know,
was it really hard
during your
first few weeks there?
Yes, very. And I came there
a few weeks later.
I needed to catch up
with all of them.
He was late
and not wearing his ID.
- He was unable to get in.
- [LAUGHTER]
Why did you come in later on?
Why not from the beginning?
That's what they wanted.
Yes, I remember that.
Say "I remember" again
and I'll punch you in the face.
Yeah. This is the first time
we've heard
a threadfin bream
speak in English.
[SILLY SFX PLAYING]
Is it your dream to be in  PBB?
I actually auditioned
for the first celebrity
edition of  PBB.
- [TETAY] Okay.
- Ahh.
But I didn't get in.
- [TETAY] I don't think I can.
- Why?
Because you'd be away
for so long.
I mean, for months.
Why? Who would you miss
in the outside world?
I mean, of course,
my family, my husband,
my kids, so...
- [VERNA] Aw!
- Right? [LAUGHS]
Husband, huh? [CHUCKLES]
No, because I can't be--
I can't afford to be away
from them even just for a week.
I'd miss them badly.
- You'd really miss them.
- Yes. Absolutely--
But what if ABS-CBN
or GMA tells you,
"You won't be inside the house,
we'll just use your voice."
What if they do that.
But as a Kris Aquino
impersonator.
- Huh?
- Ah, okay.
[IN RESTRAINED VOICE]
Housemates,
please proceed
to the confession room.
[LAUGHTER]
I have something to tell you.
Hurry up. [LAUGHS]
How about Verna being evicted.
- Verna.
- Yes, Auntie?
Go to the confession room.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Why?
- I saw the pork chop
in the kitchen.
You ate it raw.
[LAUGHTER]
Verna, you need
to cook it first.
- It's fine, it was marinated.
- Wow!
Wow!
She's so sassy. Marinated, huh?
That's what I like about Verna.
She's very "I don't care,
I'll speak in English."
- Because she feels like it.
- Confidence.
I don't eat raw.
Can you check
if the beef is tender?
[LAUGHTER]
- She speaks English well.
- True.
Foreigners are attracted to her.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Hmm...
Yes.
- Do you like foreigners?
- Are you a halfie?
- I can be.
- But are you really mixed,
or are you pure Filipino?
I think Papa was a fourth,
and Mama too.
- Chinese and Spanish.
- Your papa's only a fourth,
and your Mama too, so
your family is just half then?
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- That's funny!
- Like a lengthwise pad.
He's a looker
but not so good at math.
His family is just a fourth,
so combined, that's just half.
Are you guys still looking
for the other half?
He's not so good at fractions.
- [APPLAUSE, CHEERING]
- Whoa!
- Hey! Hey!
- [LAUGHTER]
She really is sassy!
"He's not so good at fractions."
What are the qualifications
in  PBB  for people to get in?
- To be honest--
- You've got to have a backer?
[CHUCKLES] Not really.
You just have to be honest,
especially during auditions.
You have to be genuine
with your intentions.
You have to have
a story to tell.
- [VICE] Ahh.
- She has a lot.
Stories that will inspire
Filipinos.
- Yes.
- She does.
- I inspire people.
- Yes.
Especially those
who look like me.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [TETAY] Hold on, that's an--
- No one else looks like you.
- [LAUGHTER]
You're the only one
in this world.
I can point out some
in the audience.
[LAUGHTER]
- Hey, they're our neighbors!
- I forgot.
Do you have plans to audition?
I think I can.
But I'm a hoarder when it comes
to online shopping.
- What?
- I'm a parcel... hoarder.
What does that have
to do with  PBB?
[TETAY] She won't be able
o receive it.
Yeah. I don't want Big Brother
to receive it for me.
It's always cash on delivery.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
She wants to be in  PBB
but she's worried
about her orders being
delivered while she's away.
She won't be able to receive it.
How about you?
If you audition,
do you think you'd get in?
What will be your role
in the Big Brother house?
Maybe I'll help with
the cleaning and organizing.
Stuff like that.
A sort of mother hen.
- [VICE] Tetay has OCD.
- Not really.
But I'm mad
about those crumbles.
Stuff like that.
I feel like I'd get in.
- [VICE] Really?
- But...
I think, I'm-- How about you?
- [VICE] What?
- Do you--
No thanks.
I might get into a fight there.
I might even curse Big Brother.
- Hey!
-That's all I'm going to say.
I'm annoyed at him.
He doesn't show his face
yet gives you tons of tasks.
I don't even know him.
- You were inside, right?
- Yes.
Big Brother and I just fought.
[LAUGHTER]
But you have a crush on Brent
and you,
you like River.
Tell Vince to help you out.
- Should I text him now?
- Help us out.
- Can you do it?
- Why don't we call them?
Have you met River?
[IN SOFT VOICE]
I think I haven't.
Wow, that's so demure.
[IN DEEP VOICE]
I don't think so.
[LAUGH TRACK PLAYING]
Have you seen Brent in person?
That's so sour!
What a freaking sour face!
- [LAUGHTER]
- I hate her reaction!
It's like she wants you
to be even angrier.
I've never seen
a bulldog get butterflies.
[SILLY SFX PLAYING]
I want to see him, Meme.
- You want to see him?
- [TETAY] Call him.
You're friends with him, right?
I can call them.
They're my children.
- I'm very close to them.
- Oh my gosh.
- You want me to call them?
- Yes, please.
Who do you want me
to call first?
Brent.
We were texting earlier,
but his phone was running low.
He's with-- No.
I was talking to him
and the call got cut off.
He's with Ralph.
I'll call Ralph.
- Okay.
- Gosh, Vice Ganda doesn't have
a a charger. That's crazy.
When it's runnning low,
I just throw it away.
- Borrowing chargers, huh.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Wow, it's disposable!
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
Riv-- Ralph!
Oh, he's with Brent. Ralph!
Hello. Where are you guys?
- [VICE] What?
- Why are you wearing pajamas?
We're about to sleep. It's late.
Where are you?
We're thinking of going out.
We just finished filming
It's Showtime.
We're wearing pajamas because
it's late. We're about to sleep.
It looks sunny there.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
No! It's the light in the car!
We're in the car, that's why.
- I think they're abroad.
- Or we're abroad. [LAUGHS]
I'll introduce you to my friend.
She's a Chow Chow.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Show them your dark tongue.
- She's so cute!
- What?
[RALPH]  She's exactly my type.
I'm sorry, Ralph,
but I like Brent.
[AUDIENCE CHEERS] Whoa!
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- [LAUGHTER]
You're unbelievable!
How dare you reject
my son Ralph?!
No, I called you because
she has a huge crush on Brent.
- Hi, Brent.
- Here he is.
Hello.
In my heart,
you're a  Manalo  (winner).
[AUDIENCE GUSHING]
You're the only one
in my heart.
- [AUDIENCE GUSHING]
- Aw! Oh my god!
We could turn this
into something real.
- [LAUGHTER
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
She wants to--
She wants to meet Brent.
But since I'm generous,
I'll let her meet
not just Brent.
- Ooh!
- Ralph too.
I'll let you meet
my two handsome sons.
Where are you?
Can you come here?
- Where are you guys?
[TETAY] In Switzerland.
[LAUGHTER]
I'm with Vince.
Boss, what's up?
- Join us here, guys.
- Hey!
[VINCE] Come here...
in Switzerland. [CHUCKLES]
- Come here.
- Ask them to come.
Come here. We're close.
We're just in Mother Ignacia.
Come here, okay? Bye-bye.
- See you, guys.
- Bye-bye. See you. See you.
See you, love.
[AUDIENCE GUSHING]
- "Love," really?
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
Bye-bye.
What?
[TETAY]
He's giving you a kiss, Verna!
Not so fast!
[LAUGHTER]
[SILLY SFX PLAYING]
"Not so fast."
Bye-bye. Come here now.
See you guys.
See you!
- Oh, my god.
- Wow.
- You feel pretty, don't you?
- Can we ask them to come?
- You want?
- [IN SOFT VOICE] Sure.
Hey! You act like you haven't
had your lips injected.
[LAUGHTER]
River.
Oh.
Gosh, your phone's at 7%.
It was 20% earlier.
Now it's at 7.
[LINE RINGING]
- Oh!
- River!
Is this Meme?
Oh, who's that? She's pretty.
She's pretty.
I didn't-- I didn't know
you had my number.  [CHUCKLES]
Hey, River! Introduce--
I have a friend here who's nice
but not so pretty.
My friend has a crush on Emilio.
Introduce them.
- Who is it? Oh, Emilio.
- Hi!
- [TETAY] Hi there.
- We were on a show
together, right?
[TETAY] I'm sorry?
We were on
a show together, right?
Yes, and you slept
at my place one time, right?
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- Hey!
- I don't think so.
Brent and Ralph will be here.
- Please come here.
- Come here.
- Where are they?
- Where are you?
- Amsterdam.
- [LAUGHTER]
Earlier, it was Switzerland.
Now it's Amsterdam.
We're in Mother Ignacia.
The ABS-CBN compound.
What's going on there, Meme?
We'll just have fun!
Verna fetched us some water.
We're skinny-dipping.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
[RIVER]
Come on. Let's go, let's go.
Let's go? Come here now.
Make sure you bring
your gray sweatpants, River
[AUDIENCE GUSHING]
Sure, Meme.
Emilio, Tetay is waiting
for you.
Tetay wants to meet you
in person.
- Let's go.
- Oh, sure, sure.
- Maybe in an hour.
- It's okay. Willing to wait.
You've got to be kidding.
You're just by
the compound's gate.
[SILLY SFX PLAYING]
See you in a bit. Bye-bye.
- Mwah! Mwah! Mwah!
- Bye.
Oh my gosh.
Oh, come on!
You know what,
I'm getting butterflies!
Do you think they'll have fun
once they meet Brent and Ralph?
Definitely.
I enjoy being around
Ate  Verna and  Ate  Tetay.
He called you
ate  (older sister) . [CHUCKLES]
- Fine then.
-  "Ate  Verna."
Like how you'd address
the helper. [CHUCKLES]
- [LAUGHTER]
- He'll order me around.
Hey, Brent and Emilio
are about to be here.
Fix yourselves.
Just look at you guys.
- Get dressed.
- I will.
You too, get dressed.
Prove to them
you're the most handsome.
You must have all the attention.
Dress him up.
What do we have there?
- Help me get dressed, Verna.
- Sure. Come on.
It's over here.
Can I see?
Let me see the clothes.
Where is it?
You seem to have
difficulty walking.
[LAUGHTER]
Verna, why do you seem
to have difficulty walking?
Her slippers are fine
but she walks like this.
Is your house lopsided-- Wow.
Why?
[SPEAKING GIBBERISH]
[CHUCKLES]
Wow, just look at that.
This is exactly what Jaworski's
shorts in PBA looked like
in 1973.
What would look good on him?
- This one. Do you want it?
- Let him try it on.
Hurry up!
[AUDIENCE SHRIEKING]
Hold on! They're going to see--
I think our neighbors
are trying to take a peek.
- I can hear them.
- No, that's just--
Close the window!
- Why are our neighbors--
- Window closed.
Verna, let him try it on.
Take it off.
[AUDIENCE SHRIEKING]
Oh my gosh!
- I think our neighbors got in.
- No, it's just the rain,
- I can hear them too.
- Hey, I saw you.
When you took your shirt off,
Verna was like, "Oh my god!"
[LAUGHTER]
You swallowed the corn nuts
without chewing them.
Help him get dressed!
Be careful with her hair, nanny.
Fix it.
Verna, it's backwards.
- Take it off again.
- Oh, it's the wrong side.
Take it off.
No, it was right the first time.
Change the blue.
It doesn't suit you.
No, the thingy is right here.
Change it.
Do whatever you want.
Just make sure
to dress up nicely.
We have guests.
I'll go get dressed too.
And they'll be here in a minute.
They're pretty quick.
You'll meet our guests
at our house
when we return here on...
- Gandang Gabi Vice!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[APPLAUSE, CHEERING]
Oh, look at her outfit.
She really prepared for this.
- Can you stand up, dear?
- Yes!
Wow!
She's all dressed up for
her awards on recognition day.
- I'm a Korean student.
- [TETAY] Korean student?
You really prepared
for this, huh?
Are you trying
to impress someone?
- Of course, Brent will be here.
- Wow.
You look like you have a lover
on the varsity team.
[IN DEEP VOICE]
We actually broke up.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Gang! Gang!
- We're the Geng Gang, right?
- It's a different vibe.
You don't look like
friends with him.
- Just look at Vince's outfit.
- Yes!
- [AUDIENCE SHRIEKING]
- He looks-- Yes!
Look at that.
Did you see those shoes?
Oh gosh,
Lito Lapid wore that
in his first-ever film.
- He wasn't a senator then.
- [LAUGHTER]
Meme, they're called
flare pants.
Flare pants. Nice.
And are those cowboy boots?
- Yes, cowboy boots.
- Flare pants.
That suits her.
She has a flared face.
[LAUGHTER]
You guys really prepared
for this, huh?
- Look at you!
- Why?
It's a simple look
but you look so fresh!
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
It's just a casual look
for today
because my sons might ask us
to go out later.
Just something casual.
This is how Gen Zs dress up.
Very laid-back style.
The style
doesn't look too curated.
- Not overdoing it.
- Laid-back.
Laid-back.
Just a jacket in case it rains.
- Jeans.
- T-shirt.
And the rich women
might be there.
- I'll sell them jewelry.
- Yes!
- What's taking them so long?
- [DOORBELL DINGS]
- Oh!
- They're here!
Hold on.
When the doorbell rang,
you shrieked.
Because, maybe...
It's them.
But why did you shriek too?
[CHUCKLES]
- I don't know.
- I was surprised too.
- You shrieked too.
- I just copied them!
- I heard you shriek. [CHUCKLES]
- "Aah!" He got excited.
Who do you like among them?
Is it Ralph?
[LAUGHTER]
You're not sure!
- Do it again.
- [DOORBELL DINGS]
- Aah!
[LAUGHTER]
[VERNA] Hey now, Vince!
Hey, they're here!
Who will open the door?
- Hurry up, Verna!
- I'll do it.
Oh my gosh!
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you sell ice?
- I'll punch you.
- Do you sell ice?
She's asking
if we're selling ice!
[VICE] Get her out of here!
We don't sell ice!
- Get lost!
- We don't sell ice! Go!
- We only have ice pops.
- Jeez.
[VICE] Why would someone
wearing Chanel sell ice?
- Right?
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
Oh my goodness.
You were pranked.
[TETAY] I already
imagined who it would be
when the doorbell rang.
[VICE] Vince's excitement
was for nothing.
- I don't squeal often.
- He got his hopes up.
I don't squeal very often.
[VICE CHUCKLES]
- Thanks for squealing for us.
- [VINCE CHUCKLES]
- They're almost here.
- [TETAY EXCLAIMS]
[DOORBELL DINGING]
- Uh-oh!
- It's her again.
- [DOORBELL DINGING]
- [VICE] Open the door!
No! It might be that
person looking for ice.
- I might punch them.
- Oh.
- I'll do it myself.
- [TETAY] Go ahead.
[DOORBELL DINGING]
[VERNA] Did they come back?
Oh, it opens outward.
- Hi!
- [CHEERING]
- Oh!
- Hey!
- Do y'all sell ice?
- Here they are!
- Dude! How are you?
- Oh!
- [AUDIENCE SHOUTING]
- [RALPH] Hello!
[BRENT] Haven't seen you
in a while.
Let's hug later.
I don't want to ruin my hair.
[AUDIENCE SHOUTING, CHEERING]
- Wow!
- Oh my gosh.
These are my guys.
These are my fellas.
- Wow!
- Have a seat!
- Your house is wonderful.
- Yes!
We had to move here
because Vince refuses to move
back to Big Brother's house.
We had to relocate here.
Come meet
my other housemates.
[AUDIENCE SHOUTING]
Have a seat, boys.
Feel at home.
We have food here.
- What do you want?
- What are you two doing?
- [TETAY] Oh--
- [LAUGHING SFX]
[RALPH] They're acting
all demure and shy.
[IN A SOFT VOICE]
I'll prepare your food.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [BRENT] Can we meet them?
My two housemates
are Vince and Tetay.
- Hello!
- And the other one?
That's a figurine
we bought in Baguio.
- [LAUGHTER SFX]
- Yes.
There used to be a bar there.
So that's Tetay.
- [TETAY] Hi!
- Hi, Tetay.
- Gandang Gabi.
- Vince, introduce Verna.
That's Verna.
She doesn't bite.
[LAUGHTER]
- Let's approach them.
- I'm not a dog!
- Hello.
- Hi!
- Hi there.
- Hello!
- Hi!
- How are you?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[VICE] I thought Ralph
wasn't your type?
- I thought you liked him?
- Uh...
Oh, my--
I'm confused now.
- Wow!
- [LAUGHTER]
[TETAY] Hi there, guys!
- [VERNA] River!
- Hi, Verna!
You have a beautiful...
home.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
What about me?
Hi, River.
How are you?
Hi, Verna.
[AUDIENCE SHOUTING]
Hey, Verna!
I'm showing him
I'm wife material.
- [AUDIENCE SHOUTS]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
[TETAY]
That's exactly what she is!
That's right, Verna.
You're "wipe" material.
So keep wiping the table, Verna.
Here I go!
[VICE] This is Verna.
Verna, this is Brent.
- Hi, Brent.
- It's so big...
Your heart is so big.
[EXCLAIMING]
- You have a big one too, Brent.
- A big what?
- Hey!
- [VERNA GIGGLING]
- You're a big gentleman.
- Wow!
That's Tetay.
You know Vince already.
- Yes.
- And, oh--
Emilio, come here.
Tetay's waiting for you!
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- [STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- Hello.
You finally get to meet
your uncle.
- Wow.
- There he is.
- Gee...
- All the way from Brazil.
[IN DEEP VOICE]
Are you kidding me?
I thought you had
my back, man!
[VICE CHUCKLING]
[IN NORMAL VOICE] Just kidding.
Hi, Emilio. How are you?
- Hi.
- [GUSHING, CHEERING]
- I saw that!
- Hello.
Okay.
This is Tetay and Verna.
Verna's just a nickname.
- Ah...
- Her real name is Tunying.
Tunying Taberna.
- She's Anthony Taberna.
- [VERNA LAUGHS]
- [VERNA] Anthony Taberna.
- Prepare food for our guests!
- Wow!
- Whoa.
[VICE] Come here, boys!
Have a seat!
Vince, join them.
So they'll feel comfortable.
- Relax, boys. Yes.
- Feel at home!
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [VICE] Okay, here we go.
- Wu-hoo!
Gandang Gabi,
Kapamilyas  and  Kapusos!
[IN UNISON]
Gandang Gabi,  Vice!
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
Our house is so huge,
our neighbors are inside.
- [LAUGHS]
- See?
Tonight on  GGV,
we're going to have fun
with the four CEOs of hotness
who are former
PBB  housemates.
Will their undeniable rizz
help them get through
the juicy conversations
and revelations tonight?
Gandang Gabi,  Emilio,
Brent, River, and Ralph!
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
- Wu-hoo!
- One, two, three, go!
[IN UNISON]
Gandang Gabi, Vice!
[VICE] Yes!
Good job, boys.
So how does it feel
to be on the show?
[RIVER] I mean...
Of course, we're very excited!
- Yes.
-  Gandang Gabi Vice  is iconic.
[EMILIO] It's a dream come true
to be here.
I mean, it's always been
a dream of mine
to be a guest on  GGV.
GGV  is so iconic.
You gave us  "Pak Ganern!"
and that episode with Melai.
- The one with Anne.
- [VICE] I feel so old now.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Iconic but old.
[RIVER] I watched this show
when I was a kid.
Cross your heart
and hope to die?
I was around 10 years old.
I was in grade school.
I would stay up late
just to watch.
[VICE] River may look mature,
but he's only 13 years old.
- [LAUGHS]
- [LAUGHTER SFX]
[BRENT] This was the reason I
was late for school on Mondays.
GGV's  time slot was
late Sunday evening.
[VICE] Sorry for
affecting your studies, Brent.
[BRENT]
You were a bad influence.
I want to apologize
to your parents.
I didn't mean to get in
the way of your education.
You would've graduated
summa cum laude
if we didn't air back then.
- [BRENT] Probably.
- My apologies.
But back then,
my entire family would wait
for  GGV  every Sunday night.
So, we're so happy
that it's back.
[RALPH] Yeah.
For me...
This is where we get to
show our unfiltered side on TV.
Brent actually asked production
if he could curse.
- [LAUGHING]
- Ah...
You want to show
your unfiltered side?
So, Vince...
Where can they show
their unfiltered side more?
Inside Big Brother's house
or here on  GGV?
They can be their truest,
unfiltered selves here.
[VICE] Are you sure?
- We're counting on that.
- Yes.
You'd better keep your word.
So are you ready to hear
unfiltered stories
- from our guests?
- Oh my goodness!
- [CHEERING]
- What are they hiding?
- I'm nervous.
- Here we go!
Hey! Where's their food?!
- [TETAY] Wait.
- You're not the guests!
- [VERNA LAUGHS]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
We forgot to prepare their food.
We were just staring at them.
- We were just listening.
- I told you to get started!
- [VICE] Oh my goodness.
- Where is it?
[VICE] Anyway, let's start
our unfiltered conversation.
For those of us who watch  PBB,
of course, we're not
actually inside with you,
but we always wonder:
how do you shower?
[RALPH] That's how
you start a conversation!
Is there a camera
inside the bathroom?
It's a high-definition camera.
It's got the entire bathroom
in view.
[VICE] It captures everything?
[RIVER] You can't hide from it.
How do you apply to be
the CCTV operator?
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- But, seriously...
- It's the camera's angle.
The camera is tilted up,
so it captures everything.
- It's a fisheye lens.
- It's a GoPro camera.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
[VICE] So all corners of
the bathroom are visible?
- Everything.
- Nothing is hidden.
- You can't hide.
- No, no.
How did that feel?
What was it like when
you first entered the bathroom
knowing there's
a camera installed?
[RIVER] I smiled at the camera.
- [LAUGHS]
- [VICE] Wow!
River smiled
because he's confident.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
He didn't mind
facing the camera.
Vince told me that
when he first saw the camera,
he said,
"You won't see anything!"
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
"You won't see anything!
It's tucked away!"
- [LAUGHTER]
- I walked like this!
So I could hide the goodies.
So you really looked
at the camera and smiled?
You weren't scared
or nervous to do that?
That's how we felt
on our first night.
We were hesitant
to shower then.
But we only had
five minutes to do so.
We had to do it quickly.
[VICE] How long do you take
to shower at home?
[EMILIO] I think I take
about 15 to 20 minutes.
- Yeah, around that long.
- How did you do it in five?
How do you shower
in five minutes?
It takes that long
just to get undressed.
[EMILIO] Actually, Meme,
I practiced that back at home.
My sister-in-law, Megan,
she was the one...
- [VICE] She showered you?
- No!
[LAUGHTER]
That made me nervous.
I thought Megan showered you.
She joined  PBB  before,
didn't she?
- She did!
- Ah...
She gave you a heads-up
about the 5-minute shower.
- Yes, Vice.
- My goodness.
She gave me tips.
- Mm-hmm.
- Her advice was,
"Emilio, there's a camera
in the bathroom.
It will capture everything.
Shower with
swimming trunks on."
So during my entire  PBB  stay,
I think I was the only housemate
who showered in underwear.
So what I'd do during
that 5-minute shower is,
while I was soaping
my body--
- You were soaping yourself?!
- [LAUGHS]
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
Jeez, Tetay, the one you like
talks like a little kid!
He was soaping himself!
I told you it's hard
to soap yourself!
- I told you so.
- Yeah.
Then what do you do
after soaping yourself?
- [VICE] Hey!
- [LAUGHTER]
You're not at an aquarium.
[EMILIO LAUGHS]
- Okay.
- I'm imagining it.
I would wash my underwear
at the same time.
Inside the bathroom?
- Yes.
- There's a washing machine?
- I'd wash it myself.
- How?
You'd wash your underwear
while you're wearing it?
- Yes. To save time.
- How did you scrub your body?
Did you use your junk
as a loofah?
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
[VINCE LAUGHS]
- [EMILIO] That's what I did.
- [LAUGHTER SFX]
It's like killing two birds
with one stone.
- I already showered...
- But isn't that time-consuming?
You're showering
and washing clothes
at the same time,
all in five minutes.
I practiced that at home.
- I used a timer.
- It worked?
Exactly five minutes.
We never had issues
during the shower call, right?
- Nope.
- We never fought.
You can't shower together?
- We weren't allowed.
- Ah, really?
[VICE] I sometimes shower
with Tetay
- and our friends.
- [TETAY] Yes.
Especially when
the water pressure's low.
- It's in the rules.
- "I need to rinse."
- "Can you pee on me?"
- [LAUGHTER]
- [LAUGHTER SFX]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
Was five minutes enough
for your shower, Ralph?
Vice, I couldn't do  hudhod
for four months.
- Because I couldn't...
- [VICE] What does that mean?
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- Do you mean scrub?
Scrub! I couldn't scrub!
- Where did  hudhod  come from?
- I meant to say scrub.
- Sorry, sorry.
- What a word.
Is that an Ateneo term?
[RALPH] I think so.
Is it an Ateneo term?
- I don't think so.
- Oh, I just made it up.
You didn't scrub your body
for that many months?
I couldn't because we
really only had five minutes.
There was only shampoo and
a bar of soap for each of us.
- Mm-hmm.
- Usually at home,
we have loofahs, right?
- We have body scrubs.
- Yeah.
Loofahs? We use stones
to clean our bodies.
- [RALPH CHUCKLES]
- That's all we had.
Good thing
you have fair skin.
You can't tell if you're dirty.
Do you take five minutes
to shower, River?
No, because I do my hair
and my body at the same time.
You do your hair and body
at the same time?
- At the same time.
- [LAUGHING]
Shampoo and soap
at the same time.
- [RALPH LAUGHING]
- Simultaneously.
[LAUGHTER SFX]
You wash them altogether?
[TETAY] How do you shower, Vice?
- What was that?
- How do you shower?
[VICE] I just stand there
while Ion hoses me down.
- [LAUGHTER SFX]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
He hoses me down
on full blast.
He does it while
he washes the car.
[VERNA LAUGHS]
After he's done washing me,
he goes "Next!"
Then, onto the car.
So you'd wash your head
and body at the same time.
What takes longer to clean?
The body or the head?
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Hmm...
The body.
- [VICE] Really?
- Yeah.
It's a bigger part to wash.
- [AUDIENCE SHOUTING]
- [STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes, Verna?
Verna was doing this
while you were talking.
- [LAUGHTER SFX]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
[TETAY]
She's not eating anything
but she keeps licking her lips.
Exactly.
Now, okay...
Brent, how do you shower
in five minutes?
[BRENT] First, I wash
my upper body with soap.
Then when I rinse,
the lower half gets washed too.
[VICE] Ah...
So you don't get to clean
your entire body?
[BRENT] Yeah, because
we only get five minutes.
Do you shower naked?
Emilio showers in his underwear.
- [BRENT] Yes.
- And inside our room.
We get naked in there.
- Under the sheets.
- [VICE] Oh, really?
No wonder Esnyr
doesn't leave the room.
- [RALPH SNICKERS]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- Why?
- Well, I don't know.
So that's why Klarisse
was always in the boys' bedroom.
[LAUGHS]
Klarisse liked
staying in your room.
But eventually,
you didn't feel shy
about doing that anymore.
- Nope.
- Not anymore.
We got over it after a week.
- Ah...
- We weren't nervous anymore.
And since we all did it,
it didn't feel awkward anymore.
How many months
did your season run?
- Four months.
Four months?
How many months did you stay?
- Two months.
- Why'd he leave so quickly?
- [LAUGHS]
- [LAUGHTER SFX]
- I don't know!
- [CHUCKLING]
Enlighten me.
I don't know!
You voted for me!
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- That's right!
- Yeah!
Don't ask me,
you're the ones who voted.
- You evicted him.
- We were all nominated!
We all experienced
being nominated.
Yeah, I know.
Brent never voted for me.
- He was your duo partner!
- He was!
- Ah, you two were a duo?
- Yeah.
Who were you sure
would nominate you?
Among the four of them.
[RALPH]
I'm sure it wasn't me.
- Answer the question.
- Which of them?
- Point to them.
- I think...
I think when we switched duos,
he nominated me.
[LAUGHS]
[VICE] You think Emilio
betrayed you?
I had the shortest stay
in  PBB.
- How could I vote for you?
- [LAUGHTER]
[VICE] Did you go home
before him?
I only stayed inside
for 27 days, Vice.
- Why?
- Emilio left first.
I was evicted first.
Ah, that's why you said
you voted for Emilio.
[EMILIO] They all did!
They nominated me.
When you got out
of the  PBB  house,
you were able to see
what unfolded inside.
What's something that
happened that didn't air on TV?
[VERNA EXCLAIMS]
- Something juicy.
- [TETAY] Unfiltered.
[VERNA] Yes!
Why are you looking at me?!
[VICE]
What did you do this time?
Vince did something
every night.
- [EXCLAIMS]
- Every night.
- Why'd it become about me?!
- It didn't air on TV.
- [RIVER] I swear.
- [BRENT] It'd wake all of us.
[RIVER] We'd wake up
to a certain sound at night.
[VICE] What was it?
It sounded like
something's dripping.
- It was wet!
- There were fluids!
Then when we look,
he's behind the curtain.
No, he's in the corner!
- Come on, do it!
- He was!
[VICE] He always hid
behind the curtain?
- Yes!
- No matter-- Ah.
Whatever he was up to,
it wasn't happening on his bed?
- Show it to everyone.
- Okay.
Oh, wait.
We have no curtain here.
Verna, you'll be the curtain.
- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING]
- [RALPH CHUCKLES]
[TETAY] I'm sorry,
but the curtain is a bit dirty.
[LAUGHS]
I told you
to have her dry-cleaned.
If I were the curtain,
you wouldn't be able
to finish.
- [SILLY SFX, LAUGH TRACK]
- [LAUGHTER]
She'll pretend
to be the curtain.
- Okay.
- If she were the curtain,
I'd have to hide behind her.
- And then what?
- I'd position myself like this.
Why are you on your knees?
- What were you doing back then?
- You see, Meme...
- In the  Big Brother  house--
- Oh my god!
Was there another housemate?
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SUGGESTIVE MUSIC PLAYS]
- Ooh, who was it?
- Are you telling us--
You were kneeling
in front of another housemate?
What in the cult was going on?
No, Meme! Let me explain!
In the  Big Brother  house...
Well, I'm not used
to my door being locked.
Because I always need to pee
in the middle of the night.
- You peed on the curtain?
- So we had an areola...
[VICE] You mean  arinola
(chamber pot)!
- "Areola"?
- That's nice.
My goodness.
He's handsome, but dumb.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
We had our own chamber pot
for whenever we needed to go.
[VICE] Was he peeing?
- Every night.
- It was a regular thing.
- In the chamber pot or not?
- The former.
Meme, he used
to always steal mine.
- Oh, so each housemate got one?
- Yes.
Why'd you take his chamber pot?
Did yours always get full?
- Yeah.
- Do you have a bladder problem?
[LAUGHTER]
I just really like
to drink water, Meme.
- Ah, healthy living.
- Mm-hmm.
[VICE] My mind was running
wild with my curtain theories.
Turns out he was just peeing.
Why didn't he get a catheter?
- Was that not allowed?
- [LAUGHTER]
That way,
he wouldn't have to get up.
Got it. He'd always be peeing.
But, of course, at night...
Did you ever feel or notice...
I mean, when bedtime came
and the lights were off.
You know...
There was no earthquake,
but there was a slight shaking.
[LAUGHTER]
On the other side of the room
with the mirrors, Meme...
The shaking was different.
- [RIVER] Hey, that was my spot.
- Exactly.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX, LAUGH TRACK]
[VICE] Why was the shaking
different in River's spot?
[RALPH]
Because of the wind, Meme.
- Maybe it was the cooling unit.
- No, it was you.
- Really? From me?
- Yeah. I'd always hear...
[IMITATES FART NOISE]
- [VICE] What was that?
- The far side of the room...
...everyone was farting.
- I swear!
- [SILLY SFX, LAUGHTER]
- That was our pastime at night.
- Hey! [CHUCKLES]
- [VICE] Why?
- Because...
What's up with these housemates?
They're handsome, but always
peeing and farting.
It's like they've got
body problems.
[BRENT] They had contests to see
who could fart the loudest.
[RALPH] The cooling unit was
pointed right at us.
So every time they farted...
No joke.
- They'd always have a duet!
- It was awful.
[VICE]
Who had the smelliest fart?
- Josh.
- Josh, definitely.
- He'd even lift the...
- You were the first runner-up?
He'd even lift the blanket
after farting,
- then drop it back down.
- He'd shook it out.
[LAUGHTER]
[VICE] So gross.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [TETAY CHEERS]
- So disgusting.
- How about-- Yeah.
- Wow!
She was holding a mirror
when she said, "So disgusting."
- [LAUGHTER]
- [LAUGH TRACK, SILLY SFX]
It's annoying when someone
forces you to smell their fart.
[VICE] It's irritating
if it's from others.
But if it's from your partner,
it's cute.
- [VERNA] True.
- Yeah, actually. They'll trap--
There's a certain level
of closeness
when you're messing around
with your partner.
Like when they lift
the comforter and fart,
you're like, "You're so silly!"
[TETAY LAUGHS]
"It's okay. Actually, I pooped
and didn't tell you."
So that was crazy.
Anyway. That's it?
You stayed there
for several months, right?
I assume there were moments...
Men have certain needs
they can't hold back.
They've become
common practice to them.
But once you were inside,
cameras were everywhere,
so you couldn't do
those things freely.
Almost impossible.
Did you experience
something like that
yet still go through with it
because you couldn't
hold back anymore?
[VICE] Oh, Emilio's got
something to say.
- He's ready.
- [LAUGHTER]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Never, Meme.
[VICE] Gosh, I thought you were
going to say something.
We were literally
holding our breaths.
Seriously, though.
There was this one time.
- It was like...
- [RIVER] Really?
- During the first week.
- [BRENT] You did something?
- It was--
- [RALPH] You tried it?
It was early in the morning.
I woke up, but the light
wasn't on yet.
When I looked around me,
everyone was still asleep.
Anyway, I got up.
Then I walked out of the room.
Emilio tells his stories like
he's on the witness stand.
[LAUGHTER]
- Very detailed.
- The door was unlocked.
And then I went out.
I did my morning routine,
only to be scolded
by Big Brother.
- [VICE] Why?
- Because...
...the wake-up call
hadn't rung yet.
I had just woken up on my own.
I wasn't sure why, though.
Then he angrily told me
to go back to the room.
That part wasn't aired.
- That's it.
- You wanted to share that?
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX, LAUGH TRACK]
[TETAY] Honestly, I was waiting
for something else.
[VERNA] I thought he was going
to drop a bombshell.
While you were speaking,
the audience was like...
- [TETAY] So quiet, right?
- [LAUGHTER]
[MYSTICAL MUSIC PLAYS]
- [VICE] We were hooked.
- [SILLY SFX]
Thanks for sharing
that story, huh?
It's a shame
we missed that episode.
You know,
if we could've watched it,
PBB  would've gotten
much higher ratings.
My gosh. Big Brother,
why did you edit that out?
That would've been
so historical.
[LAUGHTER]
[VICE] So silly.
But before joining  PBB,
what were you guys up to?
Were you working already?
Still studying?
- A student, Meme.
- I was still in school.
- Going to school.
- You're from Ateneo, right?
- Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
Ah, you were still in school.
Did you just graduate?
I graduated in 2022,
and then I entered showbiz.
- Ah, okay.
- There was  PBB...
You're from Ateneo. And you?
- [RIVER] I'm from La Salle.
- Ah, you?
- La Salle, too.
- You?
- Ateneo as well.
- Oh, wow. It's like...
- Ateneo, huh? Amazing.
- Two versus two.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX]
[VICE] PBB is so discriminatory.
Why only allow housemates
from prestigious schools?
You don't let those
from Matute join.
- You?
- From La Salle.
Oh, wow.
- We were from the same batch.
- The three of us, right?
- Where did you study, Verna?
- La Salle.
[LAUGHTER]
[VICE]
You mean Jose La Salle College.
[SILLY SFX]
- [VERNA] Still "La Salle."
- [VICE, TETAY CHUCKLE]
I studied in TESDA, Meme.
Which school do you prefer:
La Salle or Ateneo?
Do you like La Salle guys
better than those from Ateneo?
- Which school again, Brent?
- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING]
- I'm from La Salle.
- What?
La Salle.
- How about you?
- She wants  kasal  (marriage).
[SQUEALS]
- La Salle it is, then.
- [VICE] You prefer La Salle?
- [VERNA] La Salle, yes.
- It makes sense.
With that  masahista
(masseuse) aura.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX]
A masseuse
with muscle knots all over.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Yeah.
A masseuse who needs cupping
on the forehead.
- You like La Salle better?
- Yes, La Salle guys.
[VICE] Why? What do guys
from La Salle have
that those from Ateneo don't?
[LIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
Because I can, um...
...see something special
about them. Like--
Whenever I see Brent
on  It's Showtime,
I always hear words of wisdom.
[TETAY] You can't say the same
about Ateneo guys?
[VICE] Ralph serves as a judge
on the show.
He's actually good at it.
[VERNA]
I haven't watched him, sorry.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX]
- Ouch!
- I only see Brent's parts.
- You only watch the highlights.
- Just the highlights.
Those Brent Manalo-coded clips.
[BRENT] La Salle people really
are more special.
- [VICE] Whoa!
- Special, huh!
- Exactly!
- We're special.
- You believe that, Vince?
- I can sense something!
[VINCE] I do.
[VICE] Because you're also
from La Salle.
Let's test it.
Ateneo and La Salle guys,
please sit on opposite sides.
- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING]
- [UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's have two teams.
La Salle boys on this side,
Ateneo boys on the other side.
Okay. We'll have our own...
Mister Q and A:
Battle of Universities.
- Exciting!
- [BRENT] Oh no...
- Here we go!
- Mr. Q and A!
[VICE] Give us
your wittiest answers, okay?
- Let's see.
- Is there a math question?
- Not even one?
- No math at all.
- Is that your forte?
- Yes, math.
What program did you take?
Ralph and I were both
in Management Engineering.
- Hey, that's a tough program.
- Yes.
Management Engineering
in Ateneo is brutal.
Especially if you don't
have the money to enroll.
It's really hard.
[LAUGHTER]
- Really. What was your program?
- Advertising Management.
- You?
- Business Management.
- Ours were kind of related.
- Oh, that's nice.
Well, let's see.
Okay, round one.
This is gonna be
Ralph vs. Brent.
The issue you're going
to be debating is this.
Ralph and Brent.
Question.
Who would you rather
make out with:
a  tiktik  (bird-like vampire)
or someone with bad breath?
- Okay.
- [VERNA LAUGHS]
So, who's going
to defend the tiktik?
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Maybe they're not familiar
with it.
- I'll defend the other one.
- Yeah, I agree.
- Ask them, sis.
- Do you guys know what it is?
Verna, please describe
your species.
[LAUGHTER]
Oh my!
- [SILLY SFX]
- [CHUCKLES]
[VICE] That tongue is wild.
Like the tongue of a Chow Chow.
They're probably thinking
it's a dog breed. It's not.
[VICE] That's the tiktik. Okay.
- You'll defend it?
- I'll take bad breath.
Brent gets bad breath.
- Who'd rather make out with?
- I've got this.
Ralph said he'd rather
make out with a tiktik
than someone with bad breath.
Brent, on the other hand,
said the opposite.
Let's start with Ralph.
Go!
- Can I walk around?
- [VICE] Yes.
- Okay, here we go!
- He's all fired up.
[VICE] He's really channeling
that Miss Q and A spirit!
[EMILIO] Let's go!
- One big fight! One big fight!
- [STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I believe that if I had
to choose between the two,
to make out with a tiktik
or someone with bad breath,
I would choose the tiktik.
As we all know,
the tiktik is a creature
with a very long tongue.
We want intensity,
and the tiktik can give that
when making out.
You'll never catch me making out
with someone who has bad breath.
To be honest, I won't be able
to stand that kind of smell.
And I... thank you.
- [VICE] Wow!
- [BRENT] Very well said!
[EXCITING MUSIC PLAYING]
[EMILIO] One big fight!
- One big fight!
- [CHUCKLES] One big fight!
- Brent, I'm a little nervous.
- Good job.
- Let's go.
- But I still believe in you.
I have faith in you.
So, Brent, defend why
you would rather make out
with someone who has bad breath.
Answer!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I believe I'd rather make out
with someone who has bad breath.
Why?
The tiktik's long tongue
could hurt you.
- [VERNA] Oh!
- Always remember--
Let's cut it short.
Size doesn't matter.
Performance does.
- [VICE] Whoa!
- And I... thank you.
[RIVER] Animo La Salle
(Spirit to Fight)!
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[VICE]
What a powerful quotable quote!
"Size doesn't matter.
Performance does."
Wow.
Were you talking
about yourself, Brent?
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX, LAUGH TRACK]
[VICE] Okay.
Verna, Tetay.
Please give your comments
on their answers.
Tetay, you start.
Um, actually, what he said...
I still can't move on from that
"size and performance" quote.
Anyway.
It made me feel something.
[VICE, TETAY CACKLE]
Honestly, they both did well.
Such fresh takes.
And I couldn't help but
imagine him with a long tongue
wrapping around my ears.
- [RALPH LAUGHS]
- [SILLY SFX, LAUGH TRACK]
Imagine the French kiss.
- Your fantasy, huh?
- Yeah. And it's just...
I feel so happy, like I don't
have any problems anymore.
"It feels good to be licked
by a tiktik."
That kind of feeling.
[CHUCKLES]
[VICE] Verna!
Actually, for me...
Up until now,
I'm still confused.
- Whoa!
- [RALPH] Wow!
You do look like
you're confused.
[TETAY] Continue.
I can't say who gave
the better answer.
Unless each of them
gives a demo.
[LAUGHTER]
You want a...
- [BRENT] A performance?
- This one has a long tongue.
[LAUGHTER]
This one has bad breath.
[HUFFS]
Confirmed.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX]
[VICE]
You're not a tiktik, Verna.
- [VERNA] What am I?
- An undine.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
- Good job!
- Give it up for these two!
[VICE] So fabulous!
Okay, now let's see
how Emilio and River
will deliver their answers.
[WHOOPING]
Here's our topic!
Who would you rather live with
in the  Big Brother  house:
a ghost
or someone who ghosted you?
[AUDIENCE OOHING]
- I'll take the ghost.
- It's mine.
- I want to defend it.
- It's going to be my answer.
No, you guys had the chance
to choose in the first round.
- Yeah, it's our turn now.
- We've got this second round.
- Rock-paper-scissors?
- No, no.
- No, thank you.
- You already chose earlier.
- You had your chance.
- We'll take the ghost.
- We adjusted for you.
- Yes, we did.
[VICE] Look at Brent.
He immediately started coaching
while things got chaotic.
"Chaos, huh? I should waste
no time coaching."
[BRENT]
We value teamwork in La Salle.
- Ah, brotherhood.
- Yes.
[VICE] I get it now.
- Okay, so...
- For us, it's men for others.
- True.
- Right? Leave no man behind.
That's why we let you have
the first choice earlier.
Gosh, those quotes?
"Brotherhood."
- "Leave no man behind."
- [TETAY] We didn't have any.
[VICE] Ralph went first earlier.
So this time,
River will answer first.
River, which side are you going
to defend?
Who would you rather live with
in the  Big Brother  house:
a ghost
or someone who ghosted you?
Yours is...
- Someone who ghosted me.
- Okay.
[VICE] Now, defend why.
Why would you rather live
in the  Big Brother  house
with someone who ghosted you?
Answer!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I believe I can handle being
with the person who ghosted me.
Sure, she might not have
liked me that much.
But I'm going
to prove her wrong.
Cooking...
I will cook for her,
I will take care of her.
Um...
[STAMMERING]
I will give her a bath.
And...
- I will take care of her. So...
- [BRENT] Whoo-hoo!
- I believe-- And I thank you!
- We got this one!
Whoo! Yeah!
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Being River's partner is
kind of scary.
He's going to bathe you.
[SILLY SFX]
- [TETAY] Out of nowhere.
- [VICE] Yeah.
You're busy doing something,
then he'll start bathing you.
[TETAY] "What the heck?"
"I'm giving you a bath."
- [VICE, TETAY CHUCKLE]
- [LAUGH TRACK]
Let's see if Emilio
can defend his answer.
He said he would rather live
with a ghost
than with someone
who ghosted him.
- Answer!
- [TETAY] Go, Emilio!
- [STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
- I believe...
I'd rather live with a ghost
in the  Big Brother  house
than with someone
who ghosted me.
Because a ghost
will never leave you.
But the person who ghosted
you will leave you eventually.
They have no loyalty.
Why not pick
a loyal person, right?
That's why I'd rather pick
a ghost.
- [CHEERING]
- Yeah, baby!
People from La Salle and Ateneo
have an accent, don't they?
Yeah.
It sounds like posh baby talk.
- [VERNA] It's so posh.
- [TETAY] Something distinct...
It's like, [IMITATES ACCENT]
I'll shower you with--
- Something like that.
- [LAUGH TRACK PLAYING]
I changed my mind,
I'll go with La Salle!
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- Hey, I'm La Salle!
We don't sound like that.
[SINGING]  Two sprays,
because we're gangsta
- We sound like that.
- [LAUGHTER]
Let's give River and Emilio
a round of applause.
[APPLAUSE]
Wow.
Now, just like Tetay and Verna,
they call you
the internet snacks.
Internet snacks.
Internet
As a Gen Z, Vince, please
explain it to us.
What is the meaning
of internet snacks?
Internet snacks are those
who like to post thirst traps.
- [VICE] Oh.
- People who post online.
They're aware of being
fantasized about online.
They're aware being
fantsized online--
- Their posts are intentional?
- [VINCE] Yes.
They're enjoying the attention
from their followers.
So,
are you aware that people think
you're the internet snacks?
What do you think, River?
[AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS]
Um,
[CHUCKLES]
Sometimes I can see edits
from  Pinoy Big Brother.
Old video clips.
But you don't post videos
of yourself?
[RIVER] No.
I haven't posted anythig...
- Intentionally.
- I'm still conservative.
- Conservative.
- Oh.
Are you a virgin?
You know that, Meme.
- Why would I know?!
- [LAUGHTER]
- How would I know about it?
- [TETAY] Why would you?
[VERNA LAUGHS]
How would I know?
Do we have a relationship?!
[VERNA] Why would
you know it, Meme?
[VERNA] Tell us the truth, Meme.
Were you in Big Brother's house?
He says you know about it.
When I met them,
I already had a husband!
- That's crazy.
- Maybe you were the one
hiding behind the curtain.
[LAUGHTER]
That was Vince. That was Vince.
Conservative. So, you will
not do it deliberately?
Like you'll do it to be
objectified by your followers.
Sometimes I see some
and just pray that--
- [RALPH] Wow!
- I hope my mom doesn't see it.
Nothing?
Do we have something
compiled for River?
You said you have
nothing like that.
So what people see
isn't posted by you.
Maybe it's AI.
- Because sometimes.
- Let's see if it's AI!
Here's what we compiled.
[TETAY] Here we go.
Not that, that's a gay person.
- [LAUGH TRACK PLAYING]
- But he's pretty!
- [SEXUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
[AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
[RIVER] I have clothes on!
- Conservative.
- Ah, you have clothes on.
But you still look hot.
So it's fine if you have
clothes on, Vince?
It's fine, but like what Brent
said, there's an effect.
- Ah, there's an effect.
- Ah, an effect.
Sometimes, there's an effect
even in the way they stare.
Whenever you see posts like
that, do you react to them?
- He's my friend, so yeah!
- Vince reposts it!
[LAUGHTER]
I think you have
a lot of content like that.
- [VINCE] Me?
- Yes.
I think so, yeah, since
I like going to the beach.
Of course, when you are
on the beach,
you have to take
off your clothes.
Your top.
[VICE] Ah, okay.
So, okay.
What about you, Brent, do you
have posts or content that
you think you know
the fans will react to?
Like, you're aware of
how your followers will react.
Not really, but I like
gangster songs on TikTok.
So sometimes I lipysnc to those.
What are your intentions
when doing it?
- To look cute.
- [VICE] Oh, cute.
I'm not naked when I do it.
So it's just to act cute.
As Vince said,
you don't have to be naked.
However, it depends
on the look on your face.
Let's see.
These are compiled from you.
- [SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
- [EXCLAIMS]
- [LAUGHTER]
I look cute!
What are you doing
with your mouth?
Why is the camera angle
so low?
- Why--
- What's with your tongue?
We even got a smooch!
Wait, see!
You're sticking
your tongue out like that!
That's my mannerism.
I do that with my tongue.
You don't do that
when we hang out!
I have dry lips,
that's why I do that.
What's your intention?
So your followers
could have a prayer meeting?
To follow their parents?
To inspire them to study?
- To clout chase.
- [LAUGHTER]
[VINCE] He's being honest!
To clout chase!
What about you, Ralph?
Do you post content like that
or not?
- Admit it.
- I do have some.
- Are you aware?
- Yes.
- Are you aware of doing
Um...
Maybe...
To inspire.
[LAUGHTER]
To be honest, Meme, I...
When Emilio met me,
I was a bit chubby.
- And?
- When I was a kid
I was so chubby,
and then eventually
when I was in high school
I did judo.
I started working out then.
- So...
- Ah, because now,
- you're very proud of yourself.
- I'm more confident
- about what I have now.
- You're feel good about
yourself,
with the way you look.
You used to be
shy about yourself,
- now you want to show it.
- Yes.
- Ah, I get it.
- Yes, that's it.
Let's see if that
is how we'll feel
with what we've
compiled on Ralph.
- [SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
You look like Honesto.
[LAUGHS]
Ah.
I don't think you want to
inspire them with your body,
it's like you're
showing off your teeth.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
They can't show it
because it's cut.
- [LAUGHS]
- What?
- It's cut.
- Oh, it's cut?
Why aren't you showing it?
What's underneath?
- Are you wearing a bikini?
- [LAUGHTER]
[SILLY SFX PLAYING]
This is what I can't comprehend,
If I don't know
if it's Emilio's character,
the type to post contents like t
Are you like that?
I'm just happy, Meme.
If I'm happy, then
I want everyone to be too.
[VICE] Were you a clown?
Did you join
a clown fest before?
[LAUGHS]
What are your posts
that you think will make
your followers happy?
Ah, well...
The things I post on social
media are my memories,
my achievements,
happy moments in my life.
So when I look back
in my Instagram,
I can look back
at those moments.
- That's what I do.
- You don't post thirst traps?
Um,
I just make other people
happy by looking cute,
I wouldn't call it posting
a thirst trap.
[CHUCKLES] Do you guys
believe him?
- No!
Let's see.
[UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
- That's backstage.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Why are you walking
around the ABS-CBN
building in a tank top?
The boys dressing room is 17,
when you go to the bathroom,
you have to have gain access
through the marshal.
- [VICE] Ah.
- So,
that time, I wasn't done yet,
all I needed was my jacket,
I was early, the AC
wasn't on yet, so it was hot.
That's why I was walking
around in a tank top.
[VICE] Emilio talks like he's
explaining to his parents
- so he won't get in trouble.
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- [TETAY] It's true!
- Yeah!
- [VERNA] It's long!
- When he explains
it's like,
"Please don't hit me, daddy."
- He'll really explain.
- [EMILIO] I'm obedient, Meme.
It's like he always has a an
award every recognition day.
- [CHUCKLES]
- [TETAY] Most obedient.
- He's such a good kid.
- It's true.
But for you, Tetay and Verna,
amongst the four of them,
who's physically attractive?
[SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Wow, Verna,
look at you thinking hard!
It's as if your standards
are really high.
Verna, you've seen
their bodies. Pick one.
Hurry so I can pick next.
I'm getting hungry.
- I've made my decision, Meme.
- Yes?
- I'm picking River.
- [VICE EXCLAIMS]
[VICE] You picked him
over Brent?!
- [VERNA LAUGHING]
- You said you liked Brent!
When I picked River,
those two clapped.
[VICE] Brent's happy that
you like someone else.
Why'd you pick him?
Can you stand up, River?
- There.
- [AUDIENCE SHOUTING, CHEERING]
All right, Verna, come here.
[TETAY] You guys are
wearing similar clothes!
[AUDIENCE SHOUTS]
Verna's outfit reminds me
of a vintage suitcase.
- [VERNA LAUGHS]
- That's how they looked.
- We're matching.
- You'd find them
- in the bus's baggage area.
- [LAUGHTER SFX]
Why do you consider River
the most physically attractive?
His fit, but--
- [VICE] His butt?
- No, his fit!
- Ah, his fit.
- His outfit and he's fit.
Oh, sorry for caressing you.
[CHUCKLES]
Would you like to see it?
- [AUDIENCE SHOUTING]
- He's tempting you, Verna.
[TETAY] Go for it!
Well...
If you insist, then, sure.
Do you want to...
see this?
[LAUGHTER]
[SILLY SFX PLAYING]
[VICE] Are you going
to leave Verna hanging?
Show it!
Am I right?!
- [AUDIENCE CHEERS IN AGREEMENT]
- Are you going to show yours?
Well, take it off!
Take off your top,
I'll take off my--
[LAUGHS]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- [LAUGHTER]
Take it off!
[CHANTING] Take it off!
Take it off! Take it off!
[AUDIENCE SQUEALING]
["YUMMY"
BY JUSTIN BIEBER PLAYING]
[VICE] Your pick can't do it.
He doesn't want to.
Look no further, Verna.
He's right here.
Vince, show Verna
what she's missing out on.
- Please. Go ahead.
- [RIVER] That's right.
Get ready, Verna!
[SEDUCTIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Wait a minute, Meme!
He reminds me of the guys
in those AI short videos.
- [LAUGHS]
- What?!
Those AI short videos.
[LAUGHTER]
Where everyone fights over
the hot guy.
Are you subscribed
to videos like those?
- [LAUGHS] Yeah!
- No wonder.
- Okay.
- But, wow, Vince.
- [TETAY] Yes!
- You guys can go.
- [LAUGHTER]
- She changes her mind so fast!
You have no loyalty.
If there are internet snacks,
there are also
wild comments online.
Do you come across
comments like that?
Do people leave comments
on your thirst traps?
Have you ever been
taken aback by them?
There was one comment
that really stuck with me.
It said,
"Vince, put a baby in me."
- [AUDIENCE EXCLAIM]
- [LAUGHTER SFX]
- It was that wild.
- How did you respond?
- "Where you at?"
- [LAUGHTER]
[SILLY SFX PLAYING]
[VICE LAUGHING]
I love it!
It's that simple, right?
Don't beat around the bush.
- Make it happen.
- Yeah.
Have you read any wild comments
that shocked you, Emilio?
What post was this?
I don't think
I've encountered one yet, Meme.
The ones I've read
are quite tame.
I know the wild comments
are on X,
but I don't have an account.
- What about on Instagram?
- Instagram?
You haven't encountered
any wild comments
like the one Vince received?
I think I've read
a similar comment.
- But I ignored it.
- You didn't respond?
"Put a baby in me."
"Will it be delivered normally
or via C-section?"
[EMILIO LAUGHS]
- [VERNA] It's a doctor.
- It was the same person.
[VICE] It was the same follower
who left that comment.
- [VINCE] Yeah.
- When you read stuff like that,
how does it make you feel?
Does it offend you?
[EMILIO] Not really.
Actually, I guess...
It's somehow flattering because
I post stuff online
to make people happy.
And if that comment
makes them happy,
- then, I've done my job.
- [AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
Thank you.
What's the wildest comment
you've read, Ralph?
Wildest comment...
Actually, it wasn't a comment.
It was a message request.
That's where I read
a lot of explicit stuff.
- So...
- [VICE] On Instagram? Facebook?
Ah, Facebook.
On my Facebook page.
[VICE] You read them
in your... message requests?
[RALPH]
Yes, my message requests.
- What is a message request?
- They message my page...
- Ah, okay.
- Since we're not friends,
their message ends up there,
sort of like spam.
[VICE] So you read messages
from random people?
[RALPH] When I'm in the mood
to read comments and messages.
[VICE] What's the wildest stuff
you've read?
Okay, recently,
it was my birthday.
The message said,
"Happy birthday. God bless you."
Then two days later,
they messaged again.
They said, "Let's have sex."
- [RALPH LAUGHS]
- [AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS]
It was wild!
So wild! [LAUGHS]
Did you check
their profile photo?
- I'm sure you did.
- I did.
It was a guy.
[LAUGHTER]
- What a birthday gift.
- What about you, Brent?
I haven't read any,
to be honest.
- [VICE] Yeah, right!
- [RALPH] Sure, Brent!
- You can't fool me.
- We're on  GGV,  Brent.
- Yeah.
- Uh...
- I don't read much-- [LAUGHS]
- [VICE] No!
Nice try, Brent.
You're always online.
There was one TikTok comment
that really made me laugh.
The comment was, "Guess
where our electrical post is..."
[VICE] Huh?
What post was this from?
Just a regular, cutesy post.
[VICE] All right.
And their comment was?
"Guess where our
electrical post is..."
What?
- It's in their... [SNICKERS]
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMS]
[VICE] Oh my god.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Why are your followers
so sexual?
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- [LAUGHTER SFX]
I think they meant it
as a joke.
Jeez...
There's something wrong
with your followers.
Do you block
followers like that?
- Or no?
- [BRENT] No.
Ah, he wants some more.
- [LAUGHS]
- [RALPH] That's engagement.
- [TETAY] More posts, please.
- I don't mind.
It won't harm anyone
since it's all virtual.
But maybe if someone
said that to me in person,
then I'd be taken aback.
What if they showed you
where the pole was?
- [BRENT LAUGHS]
- "Brent, here's the pole."
[BRENT] But I really don't mind.
Okay.
What about you, River?
I don't see wild comments
either. [CHUCKLES]
- [TETAY] Yeah, right!
- [VERNA] Nice try!
[VICE] The comments on your
gray sweatpants photos alone...
[RIVER] No, but the comments
I usually see are
on posts of us
together as a group.
I see comments on
posts that we're together.
I read comments
that say,
"I have three holes
for a reason."
It doesn't sound
that dirty when he says it.
[MIMICKING RIVER] "I have
three holes for a reason."
Other comments are,
"Guess where my other hand
is right now."
- Stuff like that.
- "Guess where our pole is."
[RIVER] Yeah,
that's what I usually read.
Actually, Verna and Tetay
stalked your accounts.
They read the comments there.
What did you find?
Share what you found.
"Emilio looks like
he smells so good
even though
he wears dirty underwear."
[AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS]
- Before, yes.
- [VICE LAUGHS]
- But not anymore.
- Why?
So sometimes,
when I have a game,
since I was
a varsity player before...
- [VICE] Go ahead. Explain.
- I played basketball.
[VICE] It's okay.
Don't be afraid.
I will understand, son.
Okay, what happened?
[EMILIO] Then we got stuck
at a game...
- Watch your tone, okay?
- I'm sorry.
- Yes. Um...
- [TETAY LAUGHS]
We were stranded
there due to a typhoon.
- Mm-hmm.
- We had to stay overnight.
- I only had one pair...
- [VICE] Of underwear.
- So I just used the other side.
- [VICE] Ah...
It's okay, dear.
Nothing is wrong with that.
Thank you, Mother.
Oh, don't be too hard
on yourself.
- Okay?
- [EMILIO] Thank you.
[VICE] Whose wild comment
did you find next?
Fire away, Verna!
"I want to live in Emilio's
armpit for a month."
- [VICE] Oh...
- [AUDIENCE SHOUTS]
"I want to live in Emilio's
armpit for a month."
What's up with Emilio's armpits?
- There's an Airbnb unit.
- [LAUGHS]
You can have a party
at this Airbnb unit.
- [VERNA LAUGHS]
- You can have guests over.
[TETAY] Can we see
Emilio's underarms?
- Come again?
- Does he have nice armpits?
I don't know.
Do you have nice armpits?
- Show it!
- You want to see?
- [TETAY] Why not?
- I don't know.
Baby, your uncle wants
to see your armpit.
[TETAY IN DEEP VOICE]
Where's Emilio?
- Will that be fine?
- Let Uncle see your armpit.
How can you tell if one's
armpits are nice or not?
- They'll be the judge of that.
- Well...
Will you show
your armpit to them, baby?
- Would you like to see it?
- [AUDIENCE CHEERS] Yes!
Yes. You want to
make people happy, right?
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
This is the chance
to make them happy, Emilio.
Our audience is easy to please.
Come on, Emilio,
make them happy.
Show them your armpit.
[WOMEN SHRIEKING]
[SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
That's a lot of layers.
[CHUCKLES]
Long sleeves on long sleeves.
Denim on denim.
How many layers more,
really? Huh?
Ooh.
- [UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WOMEN SHRIEKING]
[VICE]
Uncle, you want to help him?
No, let me do it for you.
- [SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
He's taking too long--
Oh, there it is.
- [WOMEN SHRIEKING]
- ["PONY" BY GINUWINE PLAYING]
[VICE] Oh, he's flexing his arm.
Look at that.
[TETAY] Oh, yeah.
[VICE] Ooh.
Do you know who really
was swooning over that?
Our cameramen. I saw you guys.
- [PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- Did you see him?
- He was like...
- Who?
[LAUGHTER]
Especially our musician
right here.
That man. He played one key
on the piano. He was like....
[SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
I heard the key.
Meme, in fairness to him,
his armpit is flawless.
If you're hygienic,
you'd have nice armpits too.
Deodorants can be too harsh
on the skin.
The chemicals are harmful.
One can live there.
I can sleep there for one night.
What would you do?
Would you thrive there?
I'd just hang out there
and eat corn nuts.
- Mm! I'm in Emilio's armpit!
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
I think it'd feel good
to just lie there.
Don't worry, he won't allow you.
[VERNA LAUGHS]
Who's next? For whom? For...
- For...
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, what's this?
The icons are just kneeling.
- [VICE] Who's that for?
- [TETAY] Icons?
It says,
"Ralph, put me in a headlock."
[VICE] Oh!
- Oh my god.
- Oh, yeah, he does judo.
- Maybe because of Judo.
- Don't stop doing that.
- Give me a spicier one.
- [SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[VERNA]
"Official hashtag for later.
#WreckMeRalph."
[LAUGHTER]
- Huh?
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
Wreck me, Ralph.
It was from  Wreck-It Ralph.
[VICE] Wreck me, Ralph.
Wreck me, Ralph.
[TETAY] Wreck, wrecker.
"Official hashtag for later.
#WreckMeRalph." Ooh.
- Emilio, you liked the post.
[LAUGHTER]
[VICE] Emilio! Emilio, you liked
the post!
Busted!
That's not my account!
Guys, don't be too hard
on my baby! He might cry!
- Emilio, what just happened?
- [LAUGHTER]
Baby, you can explain yourself
once more. Come on.
While your other guests
are eating,
explain to your friends
what happened.
Someone is
impersonating me, Mom.
[LAUGHTER]
- That's impersonation.
- [VICE] That's not you?
- [EMILIO] That's AI.
No. No.
You'd never like this post?
Why? What's so wrong
with that post?
I don't want to wreck Ralph.
He needs to be taken care of.
No wrecking him.
- Taken care of?
- Yeah.
- So demanding.
- He needs to be taken care of.
Sorry, Vice. Sorry.
He needs to be bathed
and taken care of.
That's what you like, right?
For Emilio, son, here you go.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [VICE] What else?
[VERNA] Here's another one!
"River, just one child.
You don't even have
to pay child support."
- [SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [LAUGHTER]
That profile picture
is so fierce!
When did you take a picture
like that, Vince?
[LAUGHTER]
- Is that you?
- That's not me!
You had an outfit like that
when we went out, though.
- Vice, come on.
- [VICE CHUCKLING]
"River, just one child.
You don't even have
to pay child support."
What would you say to that,
if ever?
Where are you?
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Then he replied,
"I'm right behind you,
wearing a Brazil shirt."
- [LAUGHTER]
- [TETAY] Come here!
- Okay, what else have we got?
- Here's another.
"I'm already in my forties,
but my eyes are  glood
to River's gray pants."
- "Glood"?
- [AUDIENCE SQUEAL]
That's what's written here.
[LAUGHS]
Those gray pants of yours
trended for a good while.
[TETAY] Which gray pants?
The one he used to wear
during morning workouts in  PBB.
[VERNA] Pajama pants.
- Were those pajamas?
- No, they were...
- Sweatpants?
- Yes, sweatpants.
- And those were yours?
- Yes.
- Where is it now?
- I already burned it.
- [AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
- No, but seriously...
I was shocked
when I went outside
and saw...
- ...the microphone.
- [LAUGHTER]
Because they didn't mention
anything to me.
Of course, they wouldn't
have paid any attention!
- [VICE CHUCKLES]
- So, yeah.
When you saw that,
did that make you happy
or did you feel uncomfortable?
Not really happy.
Just amused.
- I mean...
- I see.
[VICE] So you burned it?
- Mm-hmm.
- Sorry, Verna.
I was planning to
have her wash it.
How about Brent?
Any thirst comments about him?
[TETAY] Read it!
Here's one. "Dream ride."
They posted it
with a picture of Brent.
- What?
- "Dream ride."
Their dream is to ride Brent.
Why is there a picture included?
Others only got comments.
[VICE] What was that post?
- It's a cosplay.
- What were you doing?
- You're cosplaying who?
- Deadpool.
- Why?
- Just for cutesies.
[BRENT] For Halloween.
Halloween.
[VICE] What are you looking at
down there?
[AUDIENCE GIGGLING]
Who took that screenshot?
[LAUGHTER]
Now, you're regretting
some of your posts, huh?
What else have we got?
"I'm getting married, Brent.
Please have mercy on my fiance."
[LAUGHTER]
- I like their picture.
- Verna, is that you?
- It does look like you.
- Is that you?!
[VERNA] Actually...
that's my dummy account.
[LAUGHTER]
"I'm getting married, Brent.
Please have mercy on my fiance."
Is there anything wilder?
[VICE] No more?
Alright.
So, how old are you now,
Emilio?
- Twenty-six.
- Twenty-six?
Because I see a lot of shows
on Netflix.
Shows that...
What's it called again?
Coming-of-age movies.
It's usually set in a campus
or in school,
featuring high school students
and their sexual awakenings.
When did you have
your sexual awakening?
And who triggered it?
Which Filipino celebrity
triggered your sexual awakening?
- Oh, it's--
- And at what age?
I think...
I think it happened
when I was eight years old.
- When I was...
- Wait, huh?!
Baby, I did not expect
that from you!
That's something so unbecoming
of Emilio.
It happened in grade school.
During Ateneo
grade school fair.
[VICE] Goodness, Ateneo.
[EMILIO CHUCKLES]
During the fair,
Kim Chiu visited our school,
and I thought she was
so pretty.
So, Kim Chiu is
my first showbiz crush.
- Ah.
- She caught my eye.
I was like,
"Wow, she's beautiful."
Really? You always
see her on  It's Showtime.
Yeah, it makes me
feel giddy.
- [AUDIENCE COOING]
- She makes you feel giddy?
Yes, because Kim Chiu
is really pretty.
How about Paulo Avelino?
Doesn't he make you giddy?
[LAUGHTER]
[VICE] I see.
So Kim Chiu is...
...your sexual awakening?
- I think--
- Because a crush is different
- from sexual awakening.
- What's sexual awakening?
What's the difference?
Who is the first woman
you fantasized about?
[EMILIO] Uh...
Don't say it's Mother Teresa.
I'll slap you.
[LAUGHTER]
Who did you fantasize about?
I don't know-- Ah!
I think it was
back in high school.
- Remember  Transformers?
- Transformers?!
[TETAY] Optimus Prime?!
M-Megan Fox!
- Oh, Megan Fox!
- Not the robot!
I thought you were
gonna say Shia Labeouf!
[EMILIO] No, Megan Fox.
Megan Fox is so hot.
I'm gay, but I also think
she's so hot.
[TETAY] She's my girl crush.
- She's my girl crush too.
- Megan Fox was something.
- She is something.
- There was this scene
where she was
washing the car,
and I was like,
"Wow, that's hot."
She wasn't washing the car.
She was fixing it.
Right, she was fixing it.
You seem to have
the same sexual awakening.
- We had it at the same time.
- [LAUGHTER]
We were awakened
at the same time.
You watched it together?
- So your answer is the same?
- Yeah, Megan Fox.
- Really?
- That was iconic.
Megan Fox in that movie
was so iconic.
How about in the Philippines?
Which showbiz personality
did you fantasize about?
Miss Marian Rivera,
when I was a child.
- I was around five years old.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [VINCE CACKLING]
- Five years old?!
[VINCE]
You were five years old?!
I was already alarmed
when he said he was eight!
- You had it at five?!
- [LAUGHTER]
And you came from
a very conservative family.
[LAUGHTER CONTINUES]
- Really?
- How shocking.
You said something earlier
about your values.
You said you're still a virgin
because it's in your values.
But you had your sexual
awakening when you were...
- ...five years old.
- Five years old.
- Okay. [VICE CHUCKLES]
- Yes.
You, Ralph?
I think I was around
10 years old at that time.
Angel Locsin in her  Darna
and  Mulawin  era.
- That's it.
- You, Brent?
I think it was...
- Girlie from  Girl, Boy...
- [AUDIENCE EXCLAIMS]
- Oh my gosh!
- Well, she had big boobs!
[BRENT]
And a huge mole!
- Really? Her mole?
- I'm kidding!
Her mole wasn't even real.
She ended up swallowing it.
[BRENT] But seriously...
growing up, I had a
long-time crush on Anne.
I think a lot of people
already know that.
Whenever I'm asked,
she's my answer.
She was your crush, so did
you also fantasize about her?
I have a crush on Anne.
Who did you fantasize about?
[LAUGHTER]
He can't admit it because
he sees her frequently now.
But it's true.
He fantasized about Anne.
Didn't you say you
fantasized about her
in her  Kampanerang Kuba  era?
[LAUGHTER]
I thought it was so weird.
Really, Imang?!
[SILLY SFX]
[VICE] You know these four
really well.
Who among them is quite randy?
Randy?
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER, LAUGHTER]
[VINCE] I think it's River.
River? The guy from a
very conservative family?
- [RIVER] The virgin?
- [LAUGHTER]
Who had his sexual awakening
at five?
Because River is really naughty.
He's naughty...
He makes a lot
of suggestive jokes...
He has quite a dirty mouth...
But I think that's just
his outlet or pressure valve.
Because he can't
or isn't active...
I think he only jokes about it.
Is that right?
Yeah, I do let it out.
- [VICE] Huh?
- [RALPH] You let out what?
I mean, through my jokes!
[VERNA] He slipped!
[LAUGHTER]
- That surprised me!
- Just a slip of the tongue!
- [TETAY] Wait!
- [SILLY SFX]
- I let it out through jokes.
- Defend yourself, bro.
- He's not fluent in Filipino.
- Be honest.
Where do you let it out?
Through jokes or on a tissue?
- [PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [LAUGHTER]
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
On the face. Just kidding.
[RALPH CHUCKLES] Wait, what?
[VICE LAUGHS]
He said "on the face."
- [RIVER] No, wait! I didn't--
- You idiot.
[LAUGHS] Who said that?
- Speak now!
- Volume up!
[SILLY SFX]
[VICE]
He likes those kinds of jokes,
because that's all they are.
Just jokes.
When it comes to topics
like that, he's like,
"No, this is against my values."
[CHUCKLES]
So it stays at jokes.
But you know, there are people
who seem conservative,
but deep down they're bold.
Who's the quiet one,
but actually very wild?
[CHILL MUSIC PLAYING]
- My bet's on Emilio.
- [RIVER CHUCKLES]
[VICE] Ah.
He's shy on the outside,
but he's a real shooter.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX]
Did he court anyone
inside the house?
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [AUDINCE OOHING]
[VICE]
Vince, you're my right hand.
You need to tell me everything
I don't know.
Did anything escape
Meme's radar?
Did he court anyone?
None.
[VICE] You made me wait
so long for nothing.
[SILLY SFX]
- [VICE] None?
- [VINCE] No one.
So, no crush?
And no housemate
crushing on you either?
Liars go to hell.
Of course. Um, well...
I wish I could've stayed there
longer so I could...
- develop feelings for someone.
- [VICE] But--
But you didn't fall for anyone
inside?
I think I spent way less time--
No one caught feelings for you
or felt that someone likes you?
- Oh, not at all.
- [VICE] I see.
So, I wish I could've stayed
there longer.
- Maybe...
- Maybe you and Venus
could've known each other
better.
But you got eliminated
so quickly.
We did. Maybe we could've
gotten to know someone better.
But I'm happy because even
outside the house,
we still meet each other
and I'm happy...
to see all of us thriving.
And we're all very happy
to--
Were there people inside
who's flirting with each other
that we didn't notice much
because of the editing.
Were there anyone like that?
[AUDIENCE SHRIEKING]
[VICE] Did you and AZ flirt
with each other inside
- or outside the house?
- [AUDIENCE SHRIEKING]
Um...
[VICE] Was it outside the house?
[CHUCKLING] I think...
I think, inside the house,
that's when I first met her.
It's where I truly got
to know her.
Plus, her situation inside
the house
was kind of complicated
because...
well, they already know that.
But when we got outside,
of course...
we took our time getting
to know each other.
[VICE] Wait a sec, Emilio,
who are you talking to?
My friends. [LAUGHS]
Emilio is like
your youngest child
who's always talking
by himself alone.
[TETAY] The one always
goes off alone.
Because these four, all of them
are looking at me.
But Emilio is looking elsewhere
like this.
- [MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
- [EMILIO LAUGHING]
[EMILIO] Because they're waving
at me!
- I can't just ignore them.
- [VICE LAUGHS]
He's really like those kids
with an imaginary friend!
He even explained that he can't
just ignore them waving at him.
- My son is really kind.
- [EMILIO LAUGHING]
Okay, so you two connected
- [RALPH] Huh?
- outside the house?
We didn't...
nothing really formed.
- But of course we...
- [AUDIENCE TEASING]
- we got so much closer outside.
- [VICE] I see.
[VICE] Do you know
Eme Eme Tiglao?
[BOTH LAUGHING]
I judged a show with her
together before.
She's Eme Eme Tiglao.
Since we're sharing our secrets
her anyway.
Now that it's a new season
of  GGV  here in GMA,
we have something new
up our sleeves
where our guests will drop
a bombshell for us
here at... Deep Truth!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[VICE] Deep Truth, okay?
Vince, Berna, Tetay,
come here beside me.
Here in Deep Truth,
our guests will reveal...
a deep statement.
Through thorough questioning
and investigation,
the Geng Gang and I,
my Geng Gang,
will have to guess
whether the deep statement
of our guests is a  Trot  (true)
or a  Charot  (false).
Okay?
We have to be really critical
in our discernment
because whoever gets a wrong
guess or judgment
will receive a deep punishment.
Whatever it is,
we'll find out later.
Okay.
Emilio.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Where have you been?
[INAUDIBLE]
We're already starting
and you're still dilly-dallying?
He gave this to us and said,
"Wait. I feel bad.
- I'll get chairs for you guys."
- Wow!
He's really got a world
of his own, huh?
When we go out together,
Vince is really always off
to his own world.
That's why when we go out,
we have to go in groups
because I can't just focus
my attention to him
'cause of all his shenanigans.
We were supposed to go out
the other day, right?
I said--
Ralph wasn't feeling well.
Brent had a prior commitment.
Esnyr had work.
When Vince said he's free,
"Vice, let's go!"
- "Oh, we're no longer going."
- [LAUGHTER]
"It won't push through.
They're all busy.
Brent said let's go next week."
He said," Oh, I'm free anyway.
Where are you? I'll go there."
I said, "Oh, I'm gonna play
pickleball."
He went to the pickleball court.
But you know,
that's when I proved
that I don't have to worry
about Vince.
He went to talk to all
of the players in the court
even when he didn't know them.
As I was playing I keep seeing
him talk
to a different person each time.
He went to all the courts.
I said, "I'm gonna send
my son to therapy."
- [SILLY SFX]
- [VICE] And then...
- He's very sociable.
- Yes.
He gets along easily
with anyone. Right, son?
Yeah, he can get along
with anyone.
Yes, you can leave him all alone
and you won't have to worry.
He can explore the entire
pickleball court
and make friends
with everybody.
- That's right.
- Yeah.
Okay so, where's the envelope?
Get the envelope out, Vince!
[TETAY] There it is.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[VICE] Face it towards here,
Vince. That's it.
Inside these envelopes
are deep truths that our guests
want to share with us.
We will start with...
Emilio.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Show us the deep truth
you want to reveal.
Go.
- [AUDIENCE SHRIEKING]
- [TETAY] Ooh!
"I flirted with two siblings
in one night."
- [AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING]
- [TETAY] Oop!
Are you that kind of person,
baby boy? [LAUGHING]
Emilio flirted with a pair
of siblings?!
Do you guys believe in it?
You know what, it's so
unlikely of him to do that.
But then again, when alcohol
is involved at a party
he could be feeling a little
playful that night.
Yes, he might be wasted
that time.
And I feel like Emilio
is a smart person
so he did it because he'll have
to drop them off together.
- That's true.
- They're siblings after all.
- It's not like--
- [LAUGHTER]
- Dummy!
- So he'll use his brains
- for evil?
- [LAUGHING]
Since he's smart he thought,
"Oh, I'll trick them. They're
siblings anyway."
Huh? I see. You're quite
the clever one, aren't you?
- It's possible.
- Sure.
But the term they used
is "flirt".
- What does flirting mean?
- Stand up, Emilio.
Do you think he's someone
who flirts around?
Not to mention they're siblings
and it happened in one night.
It's unlikely.
What do you think?
That's what we're here
to figure out.
Let's ask some
follow-up questions.
You ask, Vince.
Investigate it.
When was the last time
you flirted with someone?
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [AUDIENCE]  Ohh!
[TETAY] Or went partying.
Or...
did this happen at a club?
Where was this?
- [AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
- [INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
Um...
I don't really like
to party anymore.
- Maybe back when--
- [VICE] When did that happen?
- What year?
- College.
- [VERNA LAUGHS] Oh.
- College?
[VERNA] So, he did.
[LAUGHS]
- [VICE] College.
- College.
Were you out with your friends,
or did you go alone to a bar
and then see the two sisters
and decide to hit
on both of them?
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Were you sad at that time?
I was very happy.
You were very happy,
so you thought, "Why not?
Let's hit on two girls.
Let's flirt with both of them."
Is that what you were thinking?
I'll take you both home!
- Maybe he was just flirting.
- What do you mean, "flirted--"
What's the--
Maybe he means something else,
because this is a good kid.
What do you mean, you flirted?
You flirted with two women,
with two girls?
at the same time,
who happen to be sisters?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TETAY] You answer your
- mother, dear.
- Oh. Y-Yes.
You flirted?
- Ohh.
- Yes.
Were you aware
that they were sisters
that night?
- No.
- [VERNA, TETAY] Oh.
[VICE] Ah, y-you weren't aware.
Maybe one of them was
on the other side of the bar
or whatever.
How did you find out--
When did you find out
that they were sisters?
After it was over?
[VERNA LAUGHS]
When-- At the end of the night.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[VICE] Did they find out
that you were flirting with them
at the same time?
I'm not sure.
What did you feel
when you found out
the girls you flirted with
were sisters?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[VICE] Did you go,
"Success!"?
- [TETAY LAUGHS]
- [EMILIO] Surprised, of course.
[VICE] You were surprised.
You're the one who knows him.
- What do you think--
- Even you were surprised.
You didn't know
he could do that.
[VICE] Okay, it's time for
Emilio to reveal the deep truth.
But before that,
we have to guess
if it's  Trot  or  Charot.
What's your answer, Vice?
- I'll go last.
- Oh, alright.
- Ah, yeah.
- Verna will go first.
Because he knows Vince.
We might base our answers
- on Vince.
- Verna, what about you?
- I feel--
- Verna!
What do you mean
erna  (Poop)?
- Her name is Verna, not  erna .
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- Huh?
- I feel like, Vice,
- it's  Charot.
- Because?
It seems like
he's just going along
with our questions,
our follow-up questions
to confuse us.
Mm.
- Tetay?
- [TETAY]  Charot.
His answers aren't consistent.
It's like, "Uh."
He's still guessing.
Also, I sometimes base it
on how someone looks.
So you feel that,
- That--
- based on how he looks,
he is someone
who would never do that.
[TETAY] Never, never.
[VICE] Vince?
For me,  Charot , because--
[VICE] It suits you to say,
"For me,  Charot."
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
Eme  (Joke).
He said, " Eme ."
- [LAUGHTER]
- [LAUGHING]  Eme?!
[SILLY SFX PLAYING]
That's what you get
for always being with me.
Okay.
I feel like it's  Charot
because when he answers,
he does this.
Ah, yeah!
There's uncertainty
because his eyes keep moving.
Okay.
- Madlang People.
- What about you, Vice?
Do you think
it's  Trot  or  Charot ?
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [AUDIENCE]  Charot!
Trot!
- Charot!
- Trot!
[TETAY] What about you?
Trot!
Charot!
[TETAY] You're thinking
about it now, too. [LAUGHS]
[VICE] No, I feel like...
River and him
are total opposites.
River is the one
who makes dirty jokes.
He's flirty.
But when there's a girl around
or someone else watching,
aside from his friends,
he backs down.
This one, though,
looks well-behaved,
- but like he said,
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- a hunter.
- [VINCE LAUGHS]
[VICE] You said earlier
- that he's a hunter.
- He mentioned it earlier.
[VICE] Right?
So that got stuck in my head.
[TETAY] Maybe he's only a hunter
of leftover rice.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
- A hunter of--
- I feel like it's  Trot.
- Oh, only you said  Trot.
- Because, of course, right?
Yes,  Trot.
But-- Yeah,  Trot.
[LAUGHTER]
Are you sure, Vice?
Yes,  Trot!
It's a  Trot  for me.
Charot, Charot, Charot.
Trot.  For the Madlang People,
-  Charot.
- [AUDIENCE]  Charot.
[VICE] Emilio.
Its time for you to reveal
to us
- [SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- your deep truth.
Is it true that you flirted
with two sisters in one night?
Or  Charot?
Go!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Trot.
-  [VERNA] Huh?!
- [UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Is that true?
No  Charot  at all?
Is it true?
[VERNA] Oh my!
- You told us--
- You could do that?
Could you? How did it happen?
How did it happen?
[EMILIO] I don't know, Vice.
Because that party was like...
There were two...
Two stages, a pre-party,
and then an after-party.
So, the--
It lasted all day.
The party lasted all day.
- Okay.
- So...
In the afternoon...
[VICE] Was that at school?
A school party
or outside of school?
Outside of school.
I-In the...
- [LAUGHING] Outside of school.
- [VERNA LAUGHS]
And then...
[TETAY] In Katipunan.
During the day, I was
with a different person.
Then at night, I was
with someone else, too.
Why was the person you were with
during the day
gone by night?
I really don't know because
there were a lot of people.
- A lot of people who--
- Ah.
Ah, but you were flirting
with her during the day?
What level of flirting was it?
[AUDIENCE SQUEALING]
- It was just...
- He's really a hunter.
- He just keeps quiet.
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
Yeah, he's a hunter.
Because look,
he really knows how
to handle it.
Earlier, while we were
interviewing,
he was already hitting on
someone over there.
You're a proud mother
earlier, right?
He was doing this to someone.
- [EMILIO LAUGHS]
- Like that.
[EMILIO] Well, we were
just talking, Vice.
Just talking.
[VICE] Yeah, and then?
Can you do that?
Flirt with someone twice
in one day?
One in the afternoon,
one at night,
with different people.
Maybe...
Maybe if I'm single.
If you're single,
then no problem.
What time of the day were you
able to make the most out of?
The daytime or the nighttime?
The nighttime.
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING]
How did you know that
they are siblings?
Someone whispered to me.
Who? Their brother?
[EMILIO LAUGHS] No!
- And he's angry!
- A friend.
It was their brother
and he was angry.
Those were my sisters. You jerk!
[DIVINE] Bro,
those are my sisters.
[EMILIO] A friend of mine
came up to me and said,
Dude, they are sisters!
Then he gestured to them.
What happened after that?
We are all still friends.
But they don't know untill now
that you dated both of them?
I think they know.
- And you're still friends?
- Yes.
- Ah, that's great!
Because they're kind. Right?
[LAUGHTER]
[DIVINE] Your kid is funny, huh?
This kid of mine...
Sorry, dear. I've been
busy with work
I've neglected you for a while.
What his nanny taught him
was wrong.
He dated two women
in the same day
not knowing they are sisters.
- [DIVINE] It turned out fine?
- Okay.
Okay. So, you're both wrong.
All three of you.
All three of you are wrong.
So, I was right.
Next, let's try River.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
[VERNA] Oh my!
[VICE] River.
What is your deep truth?
[AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
I--
I made out...
I made out with a housemate
after going out
of the  PBB  house.
- [AUDIENCE SCREAMING]
- [VERNA] Oh!
Wait a minute.
Everyone is reacting to
I made out... Oh!
Let's ask.
Mommy?
Go to mommy.
- [VERNA] Mommy.
- Mommy?
Mommy?
Do you know what make out means?
[LAUGHTER]
- Do you?
- Do you know, mommy?
- No. [LAUGHS]
Verna, explain
what make out means.
[VERNA] Make out. That's
what you put on your face.
- [DIVINE] That's makeup!
- Ah, is that makeup?
Yes. He kissed someone.
- [DIVINE] Yes.
- Yes.
You made out with a housemate
after you got out
of the  PBB  house.
Big Brother.
Okay,
He's a virgin.
But that doesn't mean he doesn't
make out with someone.
[DIVINE] You can still
kiss someone.
- [VERNA] Yes.
- Because...
Especially those
who are still virgins.
At least they can still make out
with someone, right?
It's the least they can do.
Do you have a question?
What are you looking at?
The lapel?
- What?
- [RIVER LAUGHS]
What? What's your
question, Vince?
Even before you got out
of the  PBB  house,
did you already have something
with this person?
Nothing.
So, you developed something
with this person
when you went out
of the  PBB  house?
It started on the inside
but it really developed
when we got out of the house.
Only at that time?
Do you hang out with this person
a lot after that?
No. Just a few times.
- Ah.
- What event is that?
Event?
The afterparty of our event.
[VERNA] Is this the person
you considered a sister?
- [VICE] Sister?
- [VERNA] He has someone
he treats as a sister inside.
The one you're
closest to. Right?
- I'm close with a lot of them.
- Who's that?
Who are you referring to?
- Who?
- Xyriel.
Because their closeness
is on another level.
Sometimes, it all starts
with being
brothers and sisters.
- Right?
- [DIVINE] Until it turns into,
- "Bro, don't."
- [LAUGHTER]
Why do you know it so well?
[VERNA LAUGHS]
I had a lot of big brothers.
[LAUGHTER]
Shout out to my big brothers.
[VICE LAUGHING]
Ugly but horny!
- You know what?
- Like a raffle prize!
Those were the days.
[LAUGHTER]
Ask a question! You know him!
- Her answers!
- Am I close with her?
[DIVINE] Making
my stomach upset!
[VICE] What was your question?
Did I get close to her
inside the  PBB  house?
Not so much.
Kapuso  or  Kapamilya?
[VERNA] Oh!
[LAUGHTER]
That's a big clue.
You know who that is, Vice.
[LAUGHTER]
- You're the one--
- You're annoying.
In the end, I'll be the one
getting in trouble for this.
If Aunt Cory calls me and says,
"You know
a lot of their secrets!"
If Sir Lauren calls me in.
What happened to you
after you made out?
[RIVER] I brought her home.
- [VERNA] Right away?
- [VICE] Your house?
- No, her house.
- But after that,
are you still friends or
you became uncomfortable
with each other?
We're still friends, of course.
- Seems like nothing happened?
- Seems like nothing happened.
That's normal for kids
these days, isn't it?
It seems like nothing happened.
Maybe, it was just a kiss.
Still.
You're friends but you made out?
Wait. What type of kiss?
Only a peck?
Or a true make out session?
- Because--
- Right.
There's a difference.
[RIVER] A true
make out session.
[DIVINE, VERNA] Oh!
Also, is it okay to--
Brent is it possible to make out
with someone without a reason?
Yes.
Let's ask Emilio.
I want to know,
because...
When I saw that you
made out with someone,
was that nothing to you?
[AUDIENCE LAUGHING, SCREAMING]
Oh my god!
Someone cried, right?
Okay,  Trot.
[LAUGHING]
[VICE] Let's just ask
Brent later then.
Let's just ask him later.
Do you feel hot because
of your jacket, dear?
[VICE CHUCKLING]
[VERNA] He's sweating.
[VICE] Okay.
Uh...
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
Does she have a boyfriend now?
No.
- Single too.
- Where do you like to date?
We didn't date.
- It just happened.
- You just made out immediately?
We just went straight to it.
Did you feel guilty after that?
Did you feel guilty
after doing it?
- Mm...
- Well, what happened?
Were you under the influence
of the alcohol
or were you not drunk
but you just wanted to do it?
[VERNA] Like, intentionally.
We weren't drunk.
We just wanted to do it.
[VICE] Oh, it's because
of emotions.
We just wanted
to try making out.
After the first time,
did you do it again?
- Not anymore.
- Ahh.
- [VICE] Because he has values.
- [VERNA CHUCKLES]
He comes from
a very conservative family.
Because his family is close
to Emilio's family.
[LAUGHING]
Huh.  Madlang People,
Trot  or  Charot?
[SHOUTING]  Charot! Charot!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[VICE] Say your answer first.
[TETAY]  Charot.
- And you?
- Charot.
- What about you?
Why  Charot?
- Then he'll say, "Kidding!"
- I don't know.
[LAUGHING]
Why  Charot?
I don't think his answer
is consistent
with what he is saying.
[TETAY] Wait, wait.
It seems fake.
[VINCE] It really seems impossib
- But he seems like he'll do it.
- [VICE] Why is it impossible
for him to have made out
with a housemate?
Because I know that he's not
the type of guy to do that.
[VICE] Wow!
[TETAY] Well, why would
he show you that side of him?
"Look, dude!"
[IMITATES KISSING NOISES]
- [LAUGHING]
- [COMICAL SFX]
[VICE] Look, dude!
I have a new hobby.
[IMITATES KISSING NOISES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Vince knows about it.
- Ahh.
- [RIVER] Vince knows about it.
So their answer is  Charot.
I answered  Charot  as well.
I know you and I know that
you will never do such a thing.
[VERNA] Right, so it's  Charot.
[TETAY] You know
your kids very well.
So, River.
Did you make out
with a housemate
after leaving  Big Brother ?
What's the Deep Truth?
Trot  or  Charot?
Meme, my deep statement is...
- Charot!
- Yay!
He cannot do that.
You won't do that.
You're not that type of man.
[VERNA] Sorry, River.
- He actually avoids girls.
- [TETAY] Right?
When he goes out,
he just stands like this.
[TETAY] He keeps to himself.
I asked him before about why
he always posed like that.
He said that it was
because it was crowded.
- To avoid bumping others.
- Yes, when it's crowded.
When some girls are walking,
you may accidentally graze
their fallopian tube, right?
- [LAUGHTER SFX]
- You'd think it's a mustache.
Is that a mustache?
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
Let's go with Ralph this time.
- Ralph!
- [AUDIENCE CHEERING]
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
What is Ralph's deep statement?
[AUDIENCE SQUEALING]
"I courted AZ but
I was rejected."
I courted AZ but I was rejected.
[VICE] You courted AZ
but you were rejected?
[INTRIGUING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hey, you know the answer.
You were with them in Siargao.
You know,
when you were in Siargao,
I really thought you were
the one making a move on AZ.
I was just there
as a distraction.
[VICE] Ahh!
What do you call that?
There is a word for it.
- Wingman?
- It's not third wheel.
Like back then, with me and Ion,
Zeus was always with us.
So people who'd see us would
think I had a thing with Zeus,
but it was actually Ion
who I had a thing with.
[TETAY] A tagalong?
Yes, it's something like that.
A rebound?
No, not a rebound.
Zeus knew he was there to not
let people know about me and Ion
because we were protecting
our privacy.
My friends also wanted
to protect us.
[TETAY] He's just there
to distract people.
Yes, just to confuse people.
He courted AZ?
But do you believe
that he courted AZ?
[VICE] He courted...
As their close friend,
did Ralph really court AZ...
or was it all just fan service?
Ohh!
[VINCE] For me,
I wouldn't put my hands
over a woman's shoulders
if I didn't like her.
- [AUDIENCE SQUEALING]
- [VERNA] Hey!
- [VICE] Oh, so you like her?
- [LAUGHING]
[LAUGHTER SFX]
[VERNA] I feel offended.
[LAUGHING CONTINUES]
The three of them are
so funny, aren't they?
- [AUDIENCE] Yes!
- How hilarious.
Hurry up.
Auntie dislikes cliffhangers.
You know, it's quite funny
because AZ is already married.
- Huh?
- Which AZ?
The singer.
- KZ Tandingan!
- That's KZ Tandingan.
[LAUGHTER SFX]
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[TETAY] No, wait!
I was just joking.
That's why I kept wondering why
are we talking about her.
[VICE] Then KZ suddenly
walks in.
[SINGING "MAHAL KO O
MAHAL AKO" BY KZ TANDINGAN]
[TETAY] I kept wondering because
she and TJ seemed okay.
But yes, you should know better.
I know, the two of them
are my best friends.
- [VICE] Ohh.
- [VERNA] Ahh.
[VICE] So you think that
he really courted her?
I think so.
- That's what I feel.
- So he really courted her.
But he said that
he got rejected.
[VICE] If you were a woman,
would you reject him?
Verna, you better
answer properly.
[RALPH] You rejected me earlier,
right?
And my question really was
if she was a woman,
would she reject him?
- As if she's not a woman.
- I'm a woman, Meme!
And she really pondered it
for a few seconds too.
If I were a woman--
If I were a woman?
See? You admitted it.
[VICE] If you were human,
would you reject him?
It depends on how he will
show me his determination.
- [LAUGHTER SFX]
- No, I'll give him a chance.
- [AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING]
- Yeah.
I think I won't reject him.
Wow, Kuhol has long hair now,
huh?
- [LAUGHTER SFX]
- [CHUCKLING]
What do you think?
I don't think he courted AZ yet.
Or...
- Vince, come help me here.
- No, but I think that...
I think he really courted AZ,
but I don't think
he got rejected.
Me too. Because weren't you
AC's "super crush" back in  PBB?
That was Ralph's charm.
He was secure, he was confident.
Me too, I don't believe it.
I believe he courted AC,
but I don't believe
she rejected him.
Because when we were
at Yes Please,
you were holding her tight,
and you wouldn't let go.
You were like a police officer
who just caught a criminal.
[TETAY] Oh, that's right.
[VICE] He was holding her
until I went home.
- [TETAY] Arm-locked.
- That's right.
I saw a video of them
when it was time to go home.
- AC was passed out like this.
- [LAUGHS]
Because of how tight
he held her.
[TETAY] She was purple already?
He wouldn't let her go.
He held her like this.
- [COMEDIC MUSIC PLAYING]
- [TETAY] Like that, sis?
- ["PALAGI" PLAYING]
- Look at that!
- Oh, wow!
- I see what you're saying.
- Right?
- ["PALAGI" CONTINUES]
- So sweet.
My goodness.
- See what I mean?
- And he was rejected?
- I don't believe it.
- Same here.
Okay, let's vote.
Madlang people,  Trot or Charot?
[AUDIENCE, IN UNISON]  Charot!
- I say  Charot.
- Same here.
Me too.
Now, tell us about
your deep statement.
Did you court AC, only to
end up getting rejected by her?
Trot  or  Charot?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Vice, my deep statement is...
Charot.
[AUDIENCE CHEERING]
Tell us why it's  Charot.
Because...
AC is...
...a very special friend to me.
And honestly,
I wasn't actually rejected.
- She didn't reject you?
- [RALPH] That's right.
- So you two are dating now?
- Huh?
[VICE] You said
she didn't reject you.
- [WOMAN CHEERING]
- [WOMAN] They're dating now!
- [VERNA] Oh, wow!
- [WOMAN] Unbelievable.
[VERNA] It's ongoing?
So you weren't rejected?
[TETAY] That means
they're dating.
- [VICE] Huh?
- [TETAY] They're dating.
Or they might tell us
in their own time.
The boy's confused
because you're like that.
- You're confusing him.
- [LAUGHS]
- Tetay's saying something.
- That's why he's like that.
The only reason
why you're frustrated
is because you don't
understand their generation.
You keep taking their side,
just because you
came from abroad?
Because I'm giving
the boy a chance
to tell us about it
whenever he's comfortable.
That's why we're having
all these problems.
Why? You think
I don't understand him?
Oh, you really don't!
If you understood him,
would he act like this?!
- [AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
- Mommy!
I'm not your Mommy!
Your Mommy's over there!
Don't call me Mommy!
I don't have a child
that looks like you!
[COMEDIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Now, it's Brent's turn!
[COMEDIC SFX]
Oh my goodness.
- [VERNA] Lets go, love.
- [VICE] Hey! Hey!
[GIGGLES] Just kidding!
I'm married already.
Brent, what's your
deep statement?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Whoo!
- [AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
- [WOMAN] You've got this!
[WOMAN] My goodness!
"A superhero actually reached
out to me in social media."
- [WOMAN] Woah!
- [WOMAN 2] Woah!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
A superhero reached out to him
on social media?
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [TETAY] Go on.
Go ask him a question.
Is this the most recent Darna?
[BRENT] Huh?
[VERNA] Was it her?
Many actresses
have played Darna.
[VERNA] I was talking about
the most recent one.
- Huh?
- [AUDIENCE LAUGHS]
Oh, come on.
Lasallians are smart, right?
[AUDIENCE SCREAMS]
What are you saying?
- I don't know. I really don't.
- Was it the most recent one?
I can't remember
because it was some time ago.
- [VERNA] Ah.
- It was a long time ago.
But can you remember
the year it happened?
It was before
I went into showbiz.
Around 2019, after I graduated.
[VICE] 2019?
Was this person
already a superhero,
or did they just
recently become one?
Oh, that's a good question!
When you got a DM, was this
person a superhero already,
or did this person
become a superhero...
...a few years, or a few months
after they reached out to you?
- [LAUGHS]
- [COMEDIC SFX]
That was a good question!
- [TETAY] You know what?
- [BRENT] Uh...
Vice asks very good questions.
Vice will find out the truth.
So, this person
became a superhero...
...was this person
a superhero when--
Honestly, I don't know.
I wasn't in showbiz then, so...
I only found out they played
a superhero
when I started working.
- The person who reached out?
- Huh?
- Was it an Instagram DM?
- I found out late.
Yes, I didn't see it right away.
It was an Instagram DM?
- Yes, on Instagram.
- What did it say?
It was like, "Hi, Brent."
with a smiley face.
- [VICE] Ah.
- [VERNA] Oh.
- [TETAY] I think--
- Was it a woman?
- [BRENT] Yes.
- I see.
I mean, even Ogie Alcasid
played a superhero.
- Right.
- Vhong Navarro played one too.
- He played  Gagamboy.
- Yes.
Dolphy played a superhero too.
Getting a DM from Dolphy
would be scary.
- [COMEDIC SFX]
- Really scary.
Is this person young, or old?
- Remember  Gandara?
- I do. [GIGGLES]
He said it's a woman.
And I don't DM people.
[TETAY] Right.
People usually DM Vice.
- Ah.
- [TETAY] Right?
So, is it a young actress?
Yeah. I'd say she's young.
So, it wasn't Enteng Kabisote.
[LAUGHS]
Now, your mind is
thinking of everyone.
[VICE] So, she sent you a DM.
Did you reply to her?
No, because I didn't
see it right away.
But when I saw her in person,
she didn't seem
to recognize me.
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [VERNA] Oh.
Oh, so she was bitter about it?
[BRENT] I don't know.
Maybe she forgot about it.
[VICE] If she sent you a DM,
that means she knows you.
But when you met
her in person,
she pretended as if
she doesn't know you?
- [VICE] She got hurt.
- Mhm-hmm.
Or maybe she just
forgot about it.
- Or maybe she's just shy.
- That's possible too.
Maybe she's embarrassed
because he didn't reply.
- Yes.
- True.
- Like how could he, right?
- [LAUGHS]
She sent you a DM,
and you didn't reply.
- And she's a superhero.
- Yeah, she's a superhero.
Is she hot?
I'd say she is.
- [VICE] Sexy?
- Yes.
[VICE] Did she have
some work done?
- Huh?
- [HOSTS LAUGH]
- Good question.
- I don't know.
[VICE] You don't know.
Hey, stop that. When Vice talked
about her getting work done,
she went like this.
[VERNA] Shh! I'm not
going to disclose anything.
- [LAUGHS]
- She had something done.
She had a nose lift done,
but she hit her face after.
- [LAUGHING SFX]
- It got ruined right away.
Hey, Vince.
Go ask one last question.
Do I know her?
You do.
- [VINCE] Ah.
- [VICE] Do we know her?
- Yes.
- What about the audience?
They do.
[VICE] So, she's really famous.
[TETAY] I mean,
she is a superhero.
Does she have an ongoing show?
Oh, I'm not sure about that.
I don't think she does.
[VICE] Okay.
It's time.
- [TETAY] Okay.
- Is it  Trot,  or...
She's a superhero
without an ongoing show.
And she's hot.
[VERNA] Who doesn't have a show?
- [VINCE] He said so.
- And she's sexy.
Yeah, she doesn't have
a show right now.
So, she doesn't have
a show on-air right now?
- [TETASY] Tell us.
- [VICE] She doesn't?
- But she's pretty?
- Yeah, of course.
[VINCE] Did she ever pair up
with Joshua Garcia?
[BRENT] Huh?
[VICE] Ah!
- Ahh!
- [TETAY] Okay!
I won't say anything else.
So  Trot  or  Charot?
You go first.
I think it's  Trot.
- You?
- [TETAY]  Trot.
- And you?
- Trot.
Who do you think she is?
But he won't confirm it.
Give a clue on
who your guess is.
Uh--
- [VICE] Just a clue.
- I think, tah!
[VICE CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHING SFX]
We can't think of anyone
from your clue.
- [VERNA LAUGHS]
- [VICE] What about you?
[TETAY]
No, "ah!" is the last part.
- [VICE] Huh?
- The name just got stuck.
[VICE]
You, who do you think she is?
Her too.
- Same.
- Okay. You?
- My clue is...
- Just a wild guess.
She also entered the  PBB house.
The  PBB  house.
[TETAY] Is she a thief?
- I don't think it's her.
- [TETAY] No?
Brent is smart.
He wouldn't give away anything.
[TETAY]
So he's just misleading us?
He wouldn't give a clue
he knows we'll understand
right away.
He's very smart.
He wouldn't give it that easily.
Still, I feel it's  Trot,
but it's not
who you think it is.
Guess it yourselves.
Brent! You're stressing him out.
[VICE CHUCKLES]
Brent!
Someone approached you
via social media,
and she happens to be
a superhero.
Is it  Trot  or  Charot?
- [TETAY] What?
- I should be a gentleman.
Meme, my deep statement
is  Charot.
- I'll sit now.
- You jerk.
You're such a jerk.
It's  Trot.
Yeah!
[LAUGHING SFX]
[VICE LAUGHING]
It was  Trot,  you jerk.
You made us out to be liars.
Just kidding.
It's  Trot.
Was it  Trot?
- Was it  Trot?
- I have a crush on Anne.
[LAUGHTER]
These gossipers are thinking!
They suddenly went quiet!
This is so-- Hey!
We said if we make a mistake,
we'll do a consequence.
Who made a mistake?
I don't think it was me.
The three of them, right?
With Emilio's.
They thought it was  Charot,
but it was  Trot.
So you get a consequence.
What is the consequence?
The consequence is...
Because this is Deep Truth,
Geng Gang's faces
will be dipped
in a deep bowl with icing.
You'll dip your face
in the deep bowl
the same number of times
you made a mistake.
But you only have one mistake,
so let's go.
Where's the bowl?
There. Get the bowl, get it.
Hey, I didn't make a mistake!
All of you did
during the first round.
[TETAY] Ugh.
But there are four of these.
[VICE] Go! One, two, three, go!
[VICE STAMMERING]
Guys, can you help them?
They seem to be having
a hard time.
- [BRENT] I'll take care of it!
- [TETAY] We can manage.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [VICE] I think everyone--
- One! Two, three!
Go!
[VICE] Hey, River,
do it more for Tetay!
[LAUGHING SFX]
[VICE] Why did it stick
to Verna's face?
That makes you
more beautiful, girl.
Yes!
All right, come here now.
Guys, invite our viewers
to your events.
Go. Brent, you go first.
[BRENT]
Stay tuned for the latest season
of  PBB,  which is
PBB Collab 3.0!
It's coming very, very soon.
[VICE] Once again,
thank you for being game
in playing with us tonight,
my Gen Z friends,
Brent, Ralph, Emilio, and River!
And of course,
a very big thank you
to Moodism Furniture
Design House
for the beautiful
furniture pieces
we have here in the studio.
Thank you.
Boys, thanks for visiting us.
Did you enjoy?
Oh, you're not a guest.
You're a regular here.
- Did you have fun?
- So much.
Why do you seem anxious?
- Did you enjoy?
- Of course!
- Are you happy?
- Very much.
From your friends,
who do you think said the truth?
No one!
- No, I'm just kidding.
- We all said the truth.
You guys, really.
- Did you have fun, Emilio?
- Very much. It's very fun.
Thank you very much.
Out of all of them,
it's Emilio I haven't
bonded with that much,
so at least I learned a lot
about you tonight.
- River, did you enjoy?
- Of course, Vice.
- I hope we can come back.
- Of coruse!
When you're not
a virgin anymore.
[LAUGHTER]
- What about Ralph?
- I also had so much fun.
- Thank you for having us.
- Thank you very much, guys!
Thank you. Thank you,  GGV!
Let's hang again soon, okay?
Wow!
Kapamilyas  and  Kapusos,
see you next week
only here on your favorite vice
every Sunday night. This is...
[IN UNISON]  Gandang Gabi Vice!